POST /_bulk
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with cisco ip phone 7942","answer":"Use the Plantronics compatibility guide to see what is compatible with your phone. http://www.plantronics.com/us/compatibility-guide/"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the cisco ip phone 7970 / 7961 models?","answer":"Don’t know. Call Plantronics"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i have a polycom vvx, what adapter cable will i need to plug in this headset to?","answer":"Hi Gabrielle, what is the model of VVX?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this headset work with a samsung galaxy s6 edge cell phone? if so, which adapter does it require? is that adapter available on amazon?  thanks.","answer":"no wont work"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work for a polycom vvx phone? also, is it necessary to purchase that extra adapter if i will use only with ploycom?","answer":"Yes, but you need a cable in between the headset and the Polycom. Plantronics Part Number: 27190-01"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When you use the mute button can the person on the other end hear you putting them on mute?","answer":"Hello, the answer is no, the other person cannot hear when you are putting them on mute. :) please call 1800-683-5715 for any further questions. Thanks"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work with cisco 7942 phone? what cable i need to buy??","answer":"I would call Headsets.com in San Francisco.   They are will know.  I buy my other supplies from them  800-432-3738"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a connector that will work with a Blackberry and /or an iPhone?","answer":"I don't think so.  It connects with a regular phone type plug."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with a 2.5mm jack ?","answer":"It does not. We had to purchase the DA40 USB Digital Adapter to work with our VVX-500 phones. Part # 71800-41"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Which cord do i need to connect this to a polycom vvx600?","answer":"Hi there, you would need the U10P 27190-01 direct connect cable. Another model to consider is the Discover D701 and you would need the D100 direct connect cable with that. Below is a link for your reference and give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. https://www.amazon.com/Discover-D701-Single-Office-Headset/dp/B01GGRAOYW/ref sr 1 1?ie UTF8&qid 1480543290&sr 8-1&keywords discover+d701"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Bought this for an iphone 6, what type of adapter do I need to plug into phone?","answer":"Hi Heather, you will need the QD-3.5mm adapter. Below is a link for you. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. http://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Cable-Assy-Right-Angle/dp/B000COKYXM/ref sr 1 1?ie UTF8&qid 1463666726&sr 8-1&keywords plantronics+qd-3.5mm"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work with Lucent 6416D","answer":"I'm not sure.  I used it to plug in to my computer for use with the Vonage soft phone.  It worked great in my use case.  I'm sorry I couldn't be of more assistance."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use this with a Polycom phone?","answer":"Yes, you will also need the following interface cable below. Thank you.    https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Polaris-Headset-Disconnect-2719001/dp/B00006B7RS/ref sr 1 1?s office-products&ie UTF8&qid 1542307398&sr 1-1&keywords 27190-01"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work with a Cisco phone/system? thanks!","answer":"Hello, the HW251N has an open ended connection called a QD, which makes it compatible with different devices. In this case we would need your phone's specific model to check this. You can also find the compatibility guide directly on our official website under Support   Tools. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have a vvx311 polycom phone and would like to buy the supra plus hw251n headset.  do i need to purchase anything else to go along with it?","answer":"Hi! Yes. According to our Compatibility Guide, you will need to use the U10P quick disconnect cable in order to connect the headset to your desk phone. Please feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with my comdial impact phone, and if so do i need to purchase anything else?  i do not need wireless system.","answer":"You'll need an M22 amplifier too, and the quick-disconnect cord that goes with it. This HW251N won't plug directly into your comdial."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work with avaya phone 9611g model?","answer":"Hello! Yes, it is compatible with your Avaya phone  however, in order to be able to connect your headset you require either an M22 amplifier  or you can use quick disconnect cable called HIS cord. The part number for this cable is: 72442-41. If you have any further questions, please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team: 800-985-9815."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a way to remove the headset that goes over the head and use an adapter to over the ear instead?","answer":"Hello! No, this version is not convertible. We recommend you to check out our Encore Pro 540. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you have other questions!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What else do i need to make this compatible with the toshiba dp5032-sd digital telephone?","answer":"The Toshiba DP5032-SD has a built in headset port.  So, all you will need is an A10 Modular Cable and you are all set."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I use AT&T 1070 phones in the office. Do I need an adapter or can this go directly into the headset port?","answer":"I believe you will need an adapter."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatible with avaya 9508","answer":"Hi Jennifer, yes this headset is compatible but you will need to purchase the HIC adapter to go with the headset. Below is a link for you. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Adapter-Cable-Avaya-phones/dp/B00NNPQHAQ/ref sr 1 3?ie UTF8&qid 1466011028&sr 8-3&keywords 49323-46"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What adapter do I need to connect this to a panasonic link to cell handset?","answer":"i do not  know we purchase for use with landlines sorry"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what adapter do I need for an  lg cell phone","answer":"wont work with cell phone"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the cisco ip 7941 phone?","answer":"This headset is compatible with the Cisco 7941 phone with the additional QD Modular plug cord."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have one sided hearing/hearing aid. The way it is oriented in the picture will not work with my hearing aid. Can it also go over the left ear?","answer":"Yes.  The microphone piece can be turned, to the device can be worn on either ear."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If I have this connected to the phone or not, can I hear a ringtone from the headset and not the phone.?","answer":"Unfortunately not. You'll need a wireless headset like at the link below if you want that feature. 1-800-683-5715  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B073V99416"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What adaptor do i need to use this headset with a panasonic kx-tga6860 cordless phone?","answer":"cant do it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have an nec dt-400. what adapter do i need?","answer":"Most NEC DT series phones have a  headset " port and can use the A10 Direct Connect QD cord.  If you want outbound voice volume control, a M22 Amplifier is used.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have a 67tb caption call phone, will this work with that and do i need some sort of adapter?","answer":"Hello! Unfortunately we are unable to guarantee compatibility as your desk phone is not listed within our compatibility guide, nor we're able to recommend an accessory. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Not clear on the need for an adapter. I want to use for dictation connecting to my pc's usb port. do i need an adapter or any extras?","answer":"Hello, yes you will need to purchase a separate adapter in order to connect to your computer, which i will leave in the link below. Another great headset I recommend that does not require an adapter is the Discover D711u. Check it out below or please feel free to give us a call at 1800-683-5715 for any further questions you may have. :)  https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-DA80-USB-Audio-Processor/dp/B00W2N5D1Y/ref sr 1 3?ie UTF8&qid 1516289392&sr 8-3&keywords DA70  https://www.amazon.com/Discover-D711U-Monaural-Softphone-Warranty/dp/B076TG2QF3/ref sr 1 1?s electronics&ie UTF8&qid 1516289432&sr 1-1&keywords D711u"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"if I add a Plantronics 3.5 right angle QD cable will this head set connect directly to our IPhone 5 phones?","answer":"yes, with the Plantronics 3.5 QD cable, yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What connection is needed to use with Avaya phones?","answer":"Hi R, if you give me the model of Avaya phone you have I can help you better."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What type of plug-in end does this headset come with? Is it a regular phone cord end?","answer":"It has what we call in the industry qd cord at the end. Basically you need to purchase another cord/amp so you can use this headset with your telephone. What phone are you trying to connect the headset to?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what adapter/accessories needed for new Mitel phones?  is it the same for ShoreTel230?","answer":"Sorry guy! I don't know!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work on Avaya 9608G","answer":"Yes, but it doesn not plug in directly to the headset jack on your phone, so you need the Plantronics HIS cable, Part Number: 72442-41. I do not have this part on Amazon but I'm sure you can find it. I can order a new one for you for $45 but I'm sure you can find a used one on Amazon. Thank you, Matt"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is this product neor refurbished?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What cord do i need to purchase to use the headset with a comtel phone? (rj9 headset port)","answer":"I purchased a quick disconnect cord that connect to the phone and then headset.  Works like a charm."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with the panasonic KX-DT343?","answer":"DON'T KNOW, HAVE A NEC PHONE SYSTEM"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I would like to use this headset with a cisco CP-6921 phone. which adapter do i need?","answer":"Hi there, you need the 26716-01 cable or an m22 amplifier. Give us a call with any further questions at 1-800-683-5715."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with the Cisco CP-8811 model & i would need to buy the adapter also, correct?","answer":"Yes, it works but you need the Quick Disconnect cord, Part Number: 26716-01"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I'd like to get this for our office, we need a good wired headset for the polycom vvx501 phones.  will this plug in directly?","answer":"Hello! According to our Compatibility Guide you will need to use the Vista M22 amplifier or the DA80 adapter in order to connect the headset into your desk phone. You will need to use one of these options since the connector of the headset itself is a Quick Disconnect. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have a toshiba phone model dp5022-sdm.  what cord do i need to buy to connect it to this phone?","answer":"Hi Kerry, you will need the M22 amplifier. Below is a link for you. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. https://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B000NX3OMA/ref sr 1 2 olp?ie UTF8&qid 1472241171&sr 8-2&keywords m22&condition used"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I need some sort of adapter to use this with a Cisco IP 7945 phone?","answer":"Hi Carter, yes you will need the U10 adapter, part number 26716-01. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What adapter will I need to use with my Samsung S4 cell?","answer":"GO TO www.plantronics.com and you will find answers to your questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"do I need an adapter for a Avaya model #700504844?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this headset work with broadview networks office suite phones?","answer":"It works with all systems but usually you need the M22 amp."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this fit into my Panasonic cordless phone?","answer":"Hi Janice, you would need to get the 2.5mm to QD headset adapter to go with this headset, then it would work with your cordless phone. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this headset work with IPhone 5,6, 6+ with or without an adapter?","answer":"No, you need to buy an adapter to go from the plantronics headset to an iphone or other phone.  The end of the cable is the standard Plantronics quick disconnect.  With the adapter cable it works perfectly!  Use it all the time in my office when I disconnect from my Avaya phone and want to walk around talking on my iPhone.  Fantastic headset well worth the money!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the headset come with the base and cord?","answer":"Hi Tina, this headset comes with the headset only. You'll need the headset amplifier or direct connect cable, depending on your telephone. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with a lg 5012d phone, assuming i have the 27190-01 cable","answer":"You will require a QD to headphone cable/adapter."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this the complete headset? As in top-cap, crown races, bearings, etc.","answer":"i ordered it, but i never got it. the only thing im not to sure that it comes with is the top cap. it should come with everything else"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work on xbxo one","answer":"No they only work on the 360 xbox . I have both and use both.."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can i listen to music on my ipod and chat with friends on xbox at the same time if i use a headphone jack splitter?","answer":"You would need some kind of mixer to get it to work. Two audio signals going to one set of speakers will only play whichever is more powerful. You would also need to make sure the splitter will carry the microphone signal. Most splitters only account for stereo output, not for microphone input. If you set it up so the Xbox is only using the the microphone it could work. So the input would use you iPod to play music while the mic is going to the Xbox. The Slyr uses a USB for the mic input and an RCA red and white for stereo input. So you could plug the iPod into the RCAs with an adaptor and the USB into the Xbox. You would have to test it to verify though."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use the mix amp that it comes with on my Xbox One?","answer":"I'm not sure but I used it with my PS4. I just did the 3.5 mm plug on my friend's Xbox One."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"No one can hear me on xbox one","answer":"it says on the box that the xbox one requires additional chat adapter ether then that I have no clue since I don't have a xbox one yet"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this have a usb connector?","answer":"yeah"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Dos it work for Xbox 360?","answer":"It should work"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I own a Vizio TV that only has a green audio out (no red/white slots) and I use an HDMI with my Xbox 360. Will this headset work with my setup?","answer":"You wouldn't be able to use the mixer that comes with the headset and the only way I can think of to use the headset is with an adapter. There's a tutorial on YouTube from Skullcandy that shows how to set up on the 360."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do they hook up to the game consoles like a pair of turtle beaches would essentially?","answer":"Yes. The cable has 2 different hookups on the end, One end plugs into the audio out and the other is the USB power.  Just like turtle beaches"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work for xbox one S?","answer":"It should work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"dos the packige come with every thing to hook up to a xbox 360 ?","answer":"It comes with the USB connector and you can just plug that into the Xbox but you only need the cord (the one smaller than the 3.5mm jack) if your Xbox requires that"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"So, these are totally comparable with the Xbox One?. Any adapters needed?.","answer":"Per Skullcandy....yes it works directly with xbox.  Al"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how good are these for fps gaming?","answer":"Great...excellent sound and nice mic that you can tuck away."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What adapter do I need for Xbox one","answer":"Look up xbox one chat adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"let me get this straight. cause im not 100% sure. i can plug in the included shorter cable for a phone? the hesh 2's are too bulky for school","answer":"yup"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can you plug it in to a ps4 controller","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use it on a ps4 without an adaptor?","answer":"i am not sure of the inputs on the ps4 but it has a usb port connector and the 3.5mm jack connector also so if the ps4 is able to use any of those connections, then you can use it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it do both chat and game audio on the xbox one when using the adapter","answer":"I don't have an XBox but on my PS3, I put it all the was to game then i give it one click to the voice side. For added volume on the PS3, you can adjust voice volume under accessory."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it work with a Mac for Skype calls?","answer":"Absolutely, i own a mac and i use them all the time, also i can use them to take phone calls when im lazy. The mic is very good."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"this product works with Xbox ONE???????","answer":"Kinda, you need to buy the adaptor from Microsoft. Then buy a cable for the audio input, which is around $5. But you'll experience issues such as adjusting the mic and volume. I personally won't recommend this for the xbox one. Just get the Skullcandy SLYR for xbox one.."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"do I need an adapter to use these with xbox 360?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do they work with xbox one?","answer":"No they don't , but let's hope that Microsoft makes a wireless headset"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can you listen to music and have game audio going though the headset at the same time ?","answer":"Yes. Any headset will do that."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I need the Xbox one adapter to use the headset for the Xbox one?","answer":"Yes you will need the adaptor for use with the Xbox one.  However, I  have heard that there is a SLYR  headset coming out that is   just   for the Xbox One. I  think the price will be ninety some dollars and be sporting the Halo game look in a white coat.  So now you can buy this awesome headset and buy a 25  dollar adaptor or buy the entire thing together with a halo look,  listeners preference.  :-)"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have mic monitoring, or the ability to hear yourself speak through the headset so you are not shouting?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this connect to PS4","answer":"I am not sure. I would call Game Stop and ask them or ur local video store."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can these be used for wii u?","answer":"Good Morning!  Per Skullcandy, they should work.  Thanks!   Al"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what is the difference between these and the xb1 edition?","answer":"The only difference is sound quality, and quality of the mic"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these cups large enough for big ears over long periods of time gaming?","answer":"They are very good for long periods of time because i play cs:Go for 3-4 hours straight and no pain or anything, very comfortable. Hope this helps."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are they wireless","answer":"No, they have a really long cord."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how is it used with xbox 360 ?","answer":"Plug it in"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these compatible with Windows 8.1?","answer":"Yes its compatible with windows 8.1 and windows 10."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do these compare to Uproars in terms of sound quality?","answer":"The sound quality is really really good, but after a few years it slowly declines, but overall stays pretty loud. I once had someone mistake the sound quality for a $200 dollar pair of beats..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what about the sounds for xplosions an that kind of sounds?","answer":"The sound quality for sound effects like explosions is exceptional.  The quality of the low range of sounds is excellent so it really picks up rich sound effects."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is it good for listening music?","answer":"It is great for listening to music. It has a bass booster and bass control. Hope this will help."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with PC? If it does how?","answer":"Yes it does work on pc.   I personally just plug it into the headphone jack on my pc. If you want to use the extension cord that it come with it, you'll have to plug it into a usb port, then plug the headphones in. The headphones also come with a detailed instruction manual that shows you how to hook it up. I love my slyr headphones, and would recommend it to everyone."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How is the sound quality on a mobile phone? Do you get the same sorround sound?","answer":"It's not exactly the same because not all phones support surround sound but the quality of the sound itself is still top notch and the and it still gets pretty loud"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the in-line mixer work on PC? (Seperate chat & game audio)","answer":"Yes - it should work on Mac and PC."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What do i need to hook it up to a ps4?","answer":"Per Skullcandy, it will work directly with PS4   Thanks!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I can use these fully wireless right?","answer":"No. They are definitely corded. One cool feature: they disconnect from the earpiece as well as the other end.  If you have any problems, check to make sure that they are connected well on both ends."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will it work on the ps3?","answer":"Yes, that's the only reason I own them!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use it on playstation 4","answer":"As long as you have something that has audio components like I have, yes. I have an hdmi to component converter in order to use mine on my tv. I have an old tv. Without this, I doubt it would work. But I am not 100% sure. But doing it the way I did allowed me to use it on my ps4."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it connect wirelessly to android and ios devices?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"are these compatible with the ps3?","answer":"Yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"works with ps4? how is it with call of duty and does it drain your battery on your controller?","answer":"Gotta connect slyr to ps4 directly to use it because of the mixer and no headphone cord make it work its better for the pc."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work with the PS4?","answer":"Yes any console you just have to buy adapters  like the turtle beach Dolby dss by ear force or mic adapters I had to buy those for my xbox one"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this come with any sort of case? or bag?","answer":"It just come in a box. No storage bags."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"It works with play station 4?","answer":"Yes. It should work with PS4. :D"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with Xbox one?","answer":"The Skullcandy SLYR is compatible with the XBox One. It has adapters specifically for it, in fact."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it work with a polycom vvx 250?","answer":"Yes,it will  work with a polycom vvx 250."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work with iphone headphones?","answer":"No, this  doesn't work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with polycom vvx 400 and 410?","answer":"Yes,it work with polycom vvx 400 and 410."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"which company earphones would be compatible for this?","answer":"Depends on how you are going to use it. I used mine to connect RJ9 jack on plantronic wireless headset base to separate mic and speaker Jacks on computer. If you connect the RJ9 to a supported phone, any computer headset with separate mic and speaker plugs should work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this headset wireless with Xbox one because I can’t figure it out","answer":"You need to connect the optical cable from the transmitter to the xbox, and then connect the USB cable to the transmitter and then into your xbox. If using with the Kinect, you must connect the headset to your controller."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this headset require a separate purchase of an adapter for use with Xbox One?","answer":"This comes with everything you will need to use with xbox one."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these work with playstation 4","answer":"Well you won't be able to use the mic/sound control, but you can still use the headset by plugging the 2.5mm jack into your PS4 controller"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is is compatable with an Hp laptop ? My sons port is for headphones. Im trying to find a headset that will allow him to use that and the mic","answer":"Yes it indeed is. I've been switching between this headset and one from Razer. The cushioning is decent as well. Keep in mind, the cord is detachable for easy stowing."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work for an xbox 1?","answer":"As long as your controller has a 3.5 headset jack, which I know comes standard on the One S controllers, then yes it works with Xbox one."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do these headphones connect to the Xbox360 controller?","answer":"They connect directly to the system and your television. I use PlayStation. Hope this helps!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the headphone jack 3.5mm or 2.5mm? Will it work with the XBOX ONE headset adapter?","answer":"Low audio, bad quality"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Okay, I want to get this for my gamer son, but what will I need to make sure it works with his Xbox One?  Does it need that headset adapter?  Thanks!!","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the Xbox One?","answer":"I have a ps4 not a One so im not sure but i would think yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work without the adaptor on the second gen Xbox one controllers?","answer":"No the adapter is required"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work with ps4","answer":"Yes this works with PS4"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can i use on ps3","answer":"Yes. They work on ps3 and Xbox 360. I think it also works on ps4."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with a Mac? I need it for conference calls.","answer":"It plugs in using USB so it should work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this worm","answer":"First off I need a proper question before I can give you an answer"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this double as a headset for iPhone?  Will it work as speakers only no mic for iPhone?","answer":"yes it will. I currently use this for my day job."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this headset's game and chat audio work with both next gen consoles? (Xbox One and PS4)","answer":"Yes but you need purchase adapters to make the audio sound better and like with any console boy a sound processor to enhance audio, the processor makes my skullcandy slayers sound smooth and crisp as well as my turtle beach ear force tangos. I would recommend the Dolby dss sound processor from turtle beach"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work with the new xbox one controllers?","answer":"Yes but you need to buy the Xbox one mic adapter for it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this a wired mic?","answer":"Yea it's wired but it's a nice pair of headphones I'd definitely recommend it cuz u get ur money's worth."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this have a head phone jack or usb?","answer":"Both.  From the head set it connects via 3.5 to the controllet which connects via usb or rca."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I work in a call center and i’m looking to use these wirelessly to take calls at work? anybody use them in a similar way? it’d be nice because then i’","answer":"They are a wired headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can these headphones be used with a PS4?","answer":"Yeah, you have to plug the headset to the controller. Just 1 wire that is about 6 feet long."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the Xbox One?","answer":"Yes, but I would just save up and go for turtle beach or some other brand... these aren’t necessarily the greatest"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this a wireless headset","answer":"No it's not it does have a long wire for multiple connections"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with a newer virson Xbox One controller with the 3.5mm jack?","answer":"If it's the same jack with iPhone , then it should be fine."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this headset compatible with the xbox one?","answer":"Jes, Jes it is."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work for PC","answer":"Absolutely. It has a USB jack on it, and if you are alright with stereo you can simply plug it into the headphones port. If you use the USB, the drivers may be a bit difficult, but that'll happen with any surround sound headset. The biggest problem I've encountered so far was solved simply by opening  Devices and Printers " in the Start Menu.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are they wireless?","answer":"no"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how long is the wire?","answer":"The wire is pretty decent. It stretches all the way across my room and it's about 13 feet or so."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long will these headphones be on sale?","answer":"Till black Friday"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use this by connecting it directly into my ps4 controller","answer":"Yes you can but you will experience feedback issues,  its not worth it. Just go with the usb set up, plugging it into the controller is more of an xbox thing."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"work with xbox one???","answer":"with the stereo headset adapter with is not included"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how long is the cable?","answer":"Around 6-7'"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will the headset itself play audio","answer":"Yes I use it with my phone on trips"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with the nintendo switch?","answer":"If it has a 3.5mm output for the cable or a usb slot then it should be compatible"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this headset work with an Xbox One S controller ?","answer":"Yes, only if you have the Xbox Adapter or a new controller with a 3.5mm jack. So yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What size jack is the male end?","answer":"i use it on my ps4 an most electronics i tablets pc cell phone  does come with an adaptor like for the size of an x box  if need be smaller  the maine connection is trough usb also so you can use it in various ways mine are still in good condition they are kind of big but  don t brake easy or anything"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will these work with PS4","answer":"Yes they will"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Just want to confirm, both audio and voice are compatible on the PS4? I've seen conflicting info saying that it's only audio.","answer":"Definitely is. I have had 2 pair of these bad boys since Christmas 2013. The audio is played from the TV Audio out port with a GMX Mixer powered by a USB cable. If you want you can completely remove the GMX Mixer from play and plug it directly into your PS4 Controller. I don't recommend it unless you are in party though because you lose a lot of audio that way."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Works with an iPhone?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I need a mic filter for breathing and the pops and stuff your mouth makes","answer":"no I don't use one and haven't had any trouble."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"do these only work with the old style xbox one controller?","answer":"They will work on all Xbox one controllers."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can these switch between listening to music in stereo and talking on the phone (mono/both ears) on an iPhone via bluetooth?","answer":"umm i dont know try looking at the specs some more"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"do you recomend something else","answer":"Got mine in April and one side stopped working this week -- I've only had them for 4 months.  Customer service has yet to respond.  I'm not impressed."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can someone help me figure out how to get the mic working on the head set with a xbox one. we have the adapter cord also.","answer":"Hi J. Klenske, if your xbox one is the new version, you can just use with a normal 2 in 1 splitter cable. If your xbox one is the old version, then you have to buy a microsoft adapter to that it work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it work onxbox 360 wireless??","answer":"Sorry, it can not. it can work on ps4 with the attached cable line"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I just bought these. and can i get them to snap on anywhere i've been trying for 10 minutes now. don't want to break anything.","answer":"You have to put the individual clips on first.  Then you can attach the outer ring by putting the begs into the holes on the clips."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with the adapter to get game sounds from the PS3?","answer":"If your controller has 3,5 mm porn no adapter will be needed"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i just connect both the usb and headphone jack of the headset to my xbox instead of just my controller or just the usb can do that?","answer":"Yeah both the usb and headphone jack"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"The cable that connects the headset to the ps4, is fraying and haven’t even had a year. can i buy just the cable and not purchase a new headset","answer":"Did you try electrical tape, or cord is completely severed?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can this set be used with only the usb port?","answer":"No, USB only powers up LED light"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are headphones only good to talk with other gamers or can they be used if you want to hear the game volumn alone like a walkman?","answer":"These tangle very bad, do yourself a favor and get a decent pair of headphones."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the xbox one adapter make the audio quality better? currently i plug directly into controller and audio isn’t very good.","answer":"Sorry I do not have a Xbox one so i can't say"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these have mic monitoring? Meaning you can hear your own voice through the headset?","answer":"No, unfortunately they do not.. I too love that feature but its not available with these."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it 2019 yet?","answer":"Yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work for a switch ?","answer":"Don’t waste your money. I bought it and after 30 the mic stopped working and one side oh the headset stopped as well."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work with a nintendo switch?","answer":"Not sure don’t own 1   Sorry"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I need to buy anything extra to used in xbox one s controller?","answer":"One should not need any extra attachments to connect to an Xbox One S controller. As long as there is a 3.5 mm jack in the side of the controller facing one using it, you’re good."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this gaming headset come with an adapter?","answer":"This xbox one headset can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"We can not get the mic or headset to work with pc!  What are we doing wrong?","answer":"If you have windows 10 you have to activate the mic for Cortana so you can talk to the PC. It was a little struggle but use the help section"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these work on a laptop? With only one 3.5 port","answer":"Theres 2 ways use them theres 2 plugs put adapters u can use USB port or regular headphones port these are so awsome I love them"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can't get my Acer laptop to recognize that the mic even exists  not appearing in any control panel dropdowns. Any ideas?","answer":"Try using a headset/earphones with a mic. On some laptops- the mic isnt recognized or you cannot see it in any drop dowms- but if you plug into it with headphones/earbuds with a mic- it works just fine. Found that out during the current teleworking situation."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the gaming headset have any warranty?","answer":"YES. Please contact the seller with any problems about the ps4 headset. The company will provide 12 months of free replacement, or even a full refund for your xbox one headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I'm very interested in this headphones, but the shipping for Serbia is very expens, 77$. Can you send me this headphones some other way to cost less?","answer":"This is a great product. It'll be worth the extra cost"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are the ear cups leather or leatherette?","answer":"They aren’t real leather, however, they are comfortable"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why doesn’t it light up when I’m using it for the Xbox?","answer":"The USB has to be plugged in for the lights to come on. They do make an adapter for your controller you can buy."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these open back headphones? Doesn't look like it.","answer":"They are not"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"i cant hear sound on my xbox one with these how do i fix this?","answer":"I don’t. Didn’t have to do anything extra or special to hear out of ours, but we have a PS4."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I can't hear the sound of the headphones on both sides at the same time on ps4? how do i fix this?","answer":"Please check your ps4 settings. Steps: 1. Open Device Manager (Right Click on the Start Button and select Device Manager)  2. Click on Sound, Video and Game Controllers to drop down a list of audio software  3. Right click on the name of your audio driver and choose Update Driver Software  4. Select Browse my computer, then Let Me Pick from a list of device drivers  5. From the list of drivers, choose   "High Definition Audio Device " "  6. Install the driver  7. Restart""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Seen bunch of great reviews no bad ones seen someone say they have family members that prefer these over Astro 10’s that says a lot why So cheap ?","answer":"It is a great product so we bought another one. Cheap? Only in price...not every company needs to charge top dollar for a great product"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is the cable on this headset?","answer":"About 4-5 ft long. Longer than most other headsets, part of the reason for getting the 2 we have...and we love them"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use them on the computer no for games?","answer":"Of course, he can use the computer"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this gaming headset come with an adapter?","answer":"No. Shouldn’t need one."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"The ad states it doesn't work on Xbox with  old one ". Does that mean the older consoles 1st generation Xbox one or does that mean an older controller?"","answer":"It is probably referring to the old controllers since they don't have the 3.5 mm jacks- so you cannot use the headphones with them."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it good for player unkown battlegrounds?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it be cordless?","answer":"No. It is plug in only."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"are the headphones tight? Like does it get uncomfortable to wear after 2 or 3 hours.","answer":"No the Fit is nice but the cord is my major complaint just twist into a mangle mess."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will i need a adapter for my xbox one s?","answer":"No you can plug it right into the controller. The Xbox One S controller is compatible for 3.5mm plug so you're good."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work for Xbox 360?","answer":"NO, but it works for Xbox one slim/X and other version with 3.5mm 4 pin audio port"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i have a newer xbox one s controller (including 3.5 jack), how can i get the rgb lights and mic button to work? contoller has no usb port...","answer":"The lights will only come on if you connect the USB port into a computer. The mic works fine and is connected to the Xbox one controller"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do I know which version of the Xbox one that I have","answer":"There is Xbox one, Xbox one s, now Xbox one x. It will say on the box it came in. It doesn't matter which version this headset will work with it."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How good is the mic though?","answer":"It’s really good! It can pick up on a lot of little noises.. so when I’m playing online multiplayer I have to mute my mic so no one hears my kids screaming in the background. Also it’s super comfortable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will they  come with an in line control","answer":"No, the volume control and mute button are located on the nearcup."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you take off the mic and use the headset as headphones ?","answer":"You could use them as headphones, however there’s no need to remove the mic. If you would like to move it away from your face, simply told the mic upwards."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"My laptop has a combined mic/speaker jack, would I need an adapter?","answer":"it includes a combiner for this purpose."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these childs size also? Or mainly adults.","answer":"Although the headset is a perfect fit for all head sizes, we sincerely do not recommend use by kids below 12 as it would damage kids' hearing """}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work well for watching applications such as netflix, as well as movies on dvd or blu-ray?","answer":"Yes, I have had no problems with that application"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with the usb cable to connect to your computer?","answer":"Yes it does, and it's fantastic!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this headset noise cancelling?","answer":"Model C620 has noise cancelling built in (binaural design).  Model C610 is the same thing but does not have noise cancelling built in (monaural design).  My experience with noise cancelling headphones is that they work very effectively at blocking consistent noise like the sound of the jet engine on an airplane or the sound of the office air conditioner.  However sounds that not consistent (like a conversation carried on by nearby co-workers) is not blocked and sometimes seems to be amplified because all the other consistent noise has been blocked.  I learned this using my Bose noise cancelling headphones.  When wearing them in the office, I could hear conversations on the other side of the office that I could not hear when taking the headphones off.  This has never been much of an issue for me wearing the Plantronics C620 headset because the speakers are small enough they fit ON you ear not OVER your ear (completely covering) like the Bose.  Because of this you can still hear some background noise even with the noise cancelling feature on."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it possible to hear your own voice loud and clear (not blocked by earpiece)?","answer":"Based on the design, I would say yes. However, I do not know with certainty because I've never used them."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the suggested replacement for this, since c620 is getting phased out.  The 720/500 pinches my ears (wearing glasses).  Should I go with c320?","answer":"Hello, a great headset i'd recommend is the Discover D712u, i will include in the link below. It comes with a 3 year warranty, delivers crystal clear calls and audio, and it's very durable and built for all day comfort. Please feel free to call us at 1800-683-5715 for any further questions you may have! :)  https://www.amazon.com/Discover-D712U-Softphone-Advanced-Replacement/dp/B076JHVLD1/ref sr 1 1?s wireless&ie UTF8&qid 1512573280&sr 8-1&keywords D712u"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can my 8 year old play it?","answer":"Yes, they will pick up on it quickly... but, they may need an adult to set it up, and get it online."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatible with Indian power supply?","answer":"it uses a USB-C so anything that will take a USB-C should work, I would imagine you just need to purchase an indian USB-C plug and you will be good to go :D"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When will there be more stock?","answer":"Hang in there. Shipping dates are changing constantly and it's worth checking multiple sources frequently. There are many reports of units shipping faster than stated but if it says unavialble then I guess you can't even order it."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How fast does your internet connection need to be?","answer":"Many games do not need a good internet connection, or any internet connection at all to play. You will still need internet to download them though. The speed does not really matter in this case."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with xbox one?","answer":"sorry, Im not an xbox user."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What will be the frame rate for most games? I'm hoping for 60 fps","answer":"For oculus approved apps yes.  If you are streaming from steamvr with virtual desktop then it depends on your connection"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you record gameplay?","answer":"Yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a creative platform where you can design a room/game in VR?","answer":"None that I am aware of."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are there any multi-player games for this ?","answer":"Yes. Several as long as you know someone with another headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can you hook this to your xbox 1 ?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can i watch travel viedos on it?","answer":"Yes, you can! There a number of different video apps available for the Quest."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this game have any football games?","answer":"No they’re aren’t any football games for the Oculus Quest at the moment."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you play job simulator?","answer":"It is available on Quest"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with vrchat ?","answer":"There are certain restrictions but yes, it will work with vrchat."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will the experience be the same for someone with only one seeing eye?","answer":"Depth perception requires two eyes so it would not look the same as it would to someone who has both eyes. They may still enjoy.the experience however, I'm not sure."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Unit we rec'd didn't work so we're doing an exchange. How do we get the games we just purchased onto the new unit?","answer":"You purchase them from the app on your phone and then I believe they show up on your desktop with the 2 free ones"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How is this better or slightly different from the rift?","answer":"It requires no sensor. It requires no PC. You can play it anywhere as long as you avoid direct sunlight. It’s a lot more immersive and portable without being tethered to a wire."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How can I make it more comfortable! I try to knit hat for my forehead but it really ways on my cheeks. Any ideas","answer":"There are two solutions. Either add a battery pack or weight to the strap behind your head to balance it out so that the straps don't have to be too tight. There is a kickstarter going right now called VR Balancer.    Second solution is kinda hard to explain. Add a velcro strap between your ear and temple that runs over the top of your head and attaches to the strap on the opposite side. It will relieve some of the weight."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Son 500 d lares con todo y envi  ? Es que no me aparece ning n precio de importaci n ni de env o","answer":"No me han reenbolsado el monto y tampoco me entregaron el Oculus Quest  me estafaron"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with audio headphone?","answer":"It does not come with a headset, but it has 3.5mm headphone jacks on both sides."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this be hook up to a PC?","answer":"Not directly, but you can use Virtual Desktop or similar to stream the content from you PC through the headset and control through the Touch controller or other game controller."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this support the melody VR app?","answer":"Yes, there is Quest version of the MelodyVR app! You can find the available apps for the Quest on our website here https://www.oculus.com/experiences/quest/"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have to be connected to a phone or any other device after set up?","answer":"Only during the set up do you need a phone or a tablet, once it is set-up you do not need it any longer. Do keep in mind though I believe there are certain functions in the menus that can only be accessed by the phone or tablet, but outside of using this for development of games, you shouldn't need a phone, except setting it up."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do i need a smart phone i have a samsung tablet a gaming pc and a samsung 55 inch 4k tv but my my phone is one of those free insurance phones?","answer":"As long as you can install the Oculus app via the Google Play or Apple store I think you'll be fine."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"incluye el cable oculus link?  includes the oculus link cable?","answer":"Si"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When will they be back in stock? were can i buy them for the retail price? i don’t wanna give scalpers money","answer":"You can buy it right now. we have some in stock"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is 64gb good for quite a bit of games? And should I have gotten it through oculus instead of amazon?","answer":"not really"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do the games come with it? Or do I have to buy them?","answer":"You have to buy them, but there are many demos to try and alot of free or BETA apps as well."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this have fullbody tracking soon?","answer":"Full body tracking really needs external tracking sensors whereas Quest has internal tracking, so probably not, although anything is possible with the right add-on hardware."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Plex is my main media server (for remote access). since plex is not only quest, anyone know what will be the equivalent replacement? many thanks","answer":"You can actually use the Oculus Gallery app to connect to a Plex server and other media servers. More details are available here https://support.oculus.com/267684857518882/"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why does it keep asking for a softare update?","answer":"Never had that issue"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what is the weight of the headset?","answer":"The weight of the quiz is fine because I bought an additional had bad to handle the extra weight"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I plug this in to my pc and play steam vr games?","answer":"Oculus recently released a Beta that allows this to work. Since it is in Beta there are limits and issues. It requires very specific cables and hardware at the moment. Search the internet for Oculus Link for more information."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"1.  Why do I need a smart phone?  2.  Will an Android tablet work instead of a smart phone?","answer":"It’s needed for the setup mainly, you can also buy and install games from there or stream your VR view to the smartphone. I would think the tablet should work just fine as long as you can get the oculus app in there."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Two identical units except one has 64gb, the other 128gb--and a price of $100 that separates them. $100 for an extra 64gb??","answer":"And they pay $8.95 for a Starbuck's beverage.     Sheeple beware!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Other than more memory, is there any difference between this and the 64MG headset?","answer":"Other than storage, there isn't a difference between 128 GB and 64 GB models of the Quest."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"new amazon email says this item has be upgraded at no additional cost. Upgraded how? I've already ordered and payed for 128 gb","answer":"The email means your shipping has been upgraded. You are getting release day shipping for free, meaning you are getting the headset on the day of its release."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"So i own the ps4 vr but looking at getting an occulus what is the difference between the quest and the rift?","answer":"The Quest is a standalone gaming system, meaning the headset itself is the gaming system and contains the official App Store. The rift is PC powered, meaning you need a gaming pc capable of PCVR that you plug your headset into. The Rift is supposed to have more detailed and longer games, but you’re connected to a cord. With the Quest, you are able to play cordless (or play while charging). I don’t have a rift, but I love my Quest. It is extremely immersive and I don’t have any issues with game quality whatsoever."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can this VR be connected to a TV for another person to see and hear the game","answer":"Yes! You will need some additional equipment though. It can stream directly to google chromecast or through an iPhone to Apple TV. It may work directly with some smart TVs too."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this have a gallery feature to view 3d photos / videos like the oculus go? the person at best buy said no, but he didn't sound sure.","answer":"Yes it does."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can two people play inside the same game at the same time. And if so what is needed","answer":"It depends on the game but yes. All that would be needed is a second headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have voice chat capability?","answer":"It absolutely does! Also has pass thru vision. Tap the headset and you can see outside the headset to view your surroundings."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are you sure about the January ship date?","answer":"Yes bro order it!! Mine came quick"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What are some good recommendations for games to play on this?","answer":"Oh MAN !   Let me tell you !   I haven’t played a bad game yet.   My favorite is Arizona sunshine, especially if you love killing zombies   Space pirate (  a simple space shooter but EXTREMELY cool) that’s usually the one I showcase.   I expect you to die is an AWESOME like escape room type Game"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If you add water, will it make its own sauce?","answer":"Don't forget the oregano"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why does the 64 GB version has import fees and this one doesn't? Is it a bug?","answer":"No because they include the tax inside the purchase price. You still had to pay tax however it is not written."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Where can I demo first?","answer":"Bestbuy will most likely have demo units after release day."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If I purchase two headsets for my family, can we play multi-player games with just one purchase of the game? Or do we have to purchase the game twice?","answer":"You'll need to purchase a copy for each headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I play steam VR games with this?","answer":"There will be a cable upgrade available in the near future that will enable you to connect to a computer. That will allow you to play steam VR games."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this item ship to Hong Kong?","answer":"you can call Amazon if they ship there."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"This has 6dof unlike oculus go, but at least oculus go works fine in total darkness whereas quest refuses to let me even watch movie. ideas?","answer":"This is going to sound dumb, but I bought several of those plug in night lights that stay in the electrical socket and that was enough to allow tracking at night. Those lights also have an ambient darkness sensor and only come on in the dark, which is nice."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this oculus rift come with everything needed for beginners including the cameras?","answer":"Yes, everything you need is included."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it play Marvel Powers United?","answer":"not yet"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i return this after i open it if it is not broken.  i have a small face and i'm afraid it will be too heavy or not fit.","answer":"If you feel it’s too heavy or it is pressing against your face, you are not wearing it correctly. The back of your head is supposed to support most of the weight of the headset. The back strap needs to be lowered (but not too low).    Some people attach a powerbank to the backstrap using a cellphone holster or a bunch of Velcro stripes. The powerbank both can be used to charge your headset while playing, and can also serve as a counterweight."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will i be able to have this work on my computer in an AR type view from this headset?","answer":"Oculus team is working to turn this into a similar headset as the Rift S (eventually). However, in their OC6 conference they never mentioned supporting AR."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is storage space the only benefit between 128gb and 64gb?","answer":"That is correct. As it is meant to save the games in memory. Everything is the same"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can the quest play rift S games and can Rift S play quest games with quest users?","answer":"IDK."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this also connect with the computer?","answer":"You can connect to the computer but it is not necessary"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is the wait for shipping?","answer":"In my case was the next day"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Am i able to steam real-time vr editing from my maxed out i9 macbook pro tethered with blackmagic pro and if how if not would you know what vr to use","answer":"The Oculus Quest does not support this at this time.  The Quest is a standalone VR system that does not require a PC (or Mac) to drive it.  The computer is contained in the headset itself.  There are some unsupported apps that do allow VR streaming from a PC running SteamVR if you're tech savvy enough to install and configure them (see RiftCat/Vridge and ALVR - the better option is ALVR, it is free and works best), but they're not supported by Oculus and you may not be satisfied with the results."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"i only want this for Beat Saber. how limited is the Beat Saber catalog? and can k-pop tracks be added?","answer":"Maybe there a mod , I know there a website with a game similar to beat saver with many tracks . It's called moonrider vr"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why most quest games are $30 per uploadvr?","answer":"Because developer need money for beer."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If I'm planning to mostly use my Quest linked to steam to play games, do I need the 128 gig?","answer":"I guess not. You can save 150 USD to get the steam link and other games or accessories. But there are some huge games like Vader immortal which is almost 3gb each. But if you record videos with the headset, it will be stored on your headset storage."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What games are included with the oculus quest and to redeem the included games?","answer":"The games included are Star Wars VR Series for FREE . Includes Episodes 1-3 and Lightsaber Dojos. And you do not have to redeem the games because they are already included"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the quest box come shrink wrapped?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this oculus quest fit a ten year old eyes? Is the view finder adjustable? ""","answer":"It fits my 12 year old and he wears glasses. The spacing is adjustable"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long does a charge last?","answer":"Not sure exactly how long, but long enough to get your oculus fix before putting it back on the recharge."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work with Yealink T46G phones?","answer":"The headsets will work., but the adapters will not.    Here is what you should consider if you like this system :  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00NQC389Y?m A1PBDPFFCAVYZF&ref  v sp detail page"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"After buying this can it just hook up to the pc and play, or do i have to spend another 600$ jist to get it to work?","answer":"So it all in one. You don't need a PC at all. You have to attach it to your phone to help setup(connect to wifi and other things). They have slim amount free game but you will have to buy some. Most are around 20 to 30 dollars. They are working to streaming PC games to your head set but that is not the charm of oculus quest."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do you get games for it?","answer":"oculus store....in console"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have Amazon Prime and Netflix apps?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this I am affect your vision","answer":"I have had no problem with my vision after using the device"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When is it coming out","answer":"OUt for 2 months already. I got mine on Amazon"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you get the game virtual rickality on the quest?","answer":"No.  Not at this time.  This title is for the Oculus Rift which is a different VR headset and requires a PC."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"whats the import duty for india?","answer":"I'm not sure"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with a mac and a sonnet egfx breakaway puck radeon rx 570? for a online training program?","answer":"It does NOT work with a PC - it is a standalone VR Headset using apps built in the headset. Unsure what you are trying to train on - there are multiple apps I would suggest you look for your specific use and search for apps that can achieve that."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will my already purchased oculus rift games I bought work on quest or will I have to purchase them again","answer":"It depends on the gaming company . Some with games will play on the oculus quest for free. Check with the game you order on the roof to see if it crosses over to the course for free"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When will my credit card be charged?  Once the item is shipped?","answer":"Yes, I believe that a lot of online retailers, like Amazon only process the charge at the same time the item is being shipped."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What day will it be delivered if it’s in stock on July 30th?","answer":"Bad question! In stock is a physical location. Delivery depends on variables like distance, carriers available, shipping standard, overnight etc. I"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this be a prime item? In case it is damaged or needs to be returned for any reason?","answer":"As of right now it is sold by Amazon and labeled as a prime item. Amazon will accept your return as usual regardless whether it is labeled as a prime item, as long as it’s sold by them."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why is this one cheaper then the one on the oculus website","answer":"same price everywhere"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you attach a hard drive to it ?","answer":"No. There is no current way to expand the memory."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a protection plan for the oculus all in one vr?","answer":"Not that I am aware of"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I develop little apps for fun on this if I am so inclined? (Not to publish, just for learning)","answer":"No, unless you enable developer mode."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"if you connect it to a pc is it going to take storage from the pc instead?","answer":"Yea"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When does the 128 version be available ?","answer":"Know I don’t"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"van it be connected to a pc to play pc games?","answer":"You can connect it it to a PC to transfer files but not to play PC games. It's a standalone device."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I got the wrong type of plug in and can’t use  it in my wall to charge....  can someone help?  !","answer":"Hello.  You'd need to get an adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you move around?","answer":"Yes supports up to 25’ x 25’ I believe, way more space than I have."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you have to have a Facebook account for using  it or download content ?","answer":"No. You can use a Facebook account but an oculus account works too.  You need to have an account to download content."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why is it selling for so much.?This is price gouging. wait till after Christmas","answer":"Oculus is spectacular,"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you watch the players play on a tv screen?","answer":"Yes, if you have a smart tv, it may already have capability, if not you buy Google chrome it plugs right into tv and you can cast it to tv. Otherwise they can play without you watching, speakers are in headset. This is truly a awesome adventure"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use this abroad? Plan to travel with it.","answer":"Definitely."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"The controllers usually freeze and only way to fix then is taking out the battery, any fix 4 that?","answer":"Not that I’m aware of. Mine only froze a couple of times so it wasn’t that big of an issue. Perhaps you should contact the company for further information."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is Skyrim Elder scrolls avaliable on the app store?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What operating system does this run on since it does not require a desktop PC?","answer":"Android"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you attach a hard drive to it","answer":"There is no way to expand the memory."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can creed, for quest, play against rift/s when they're on steam or oculus?","answer":"On YouTube there are guys who seem to make some kind of a living out of reviewing products, the Oculus Quest included.  Some names that come to mind are Eric for President, Tyco Tech, Ramarcus, Oasis, and probably a whole slew of others.  If you put that question in the comments section of their reviews I’m sure you’ll get an answer.  Just make a copy of that question and paste into as many reviews as you can.  Good luck."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the price for this 128 GB Model?","answer":"$499.99 and if you buy it from some other Companies it’s $529 plus $49 in shipping costs but if you buy from Amazon is shipping is free"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will there be an hdmi port to plug into?","answer":"No, there is no HDMI port, but there does appear to be a way to stream the content to a chromecast device using the oculus app on your phone."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there going to be a fullbody tracking for this?","answer":"The quest tracks your hands And head movement"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What’s the age range for this game?","answer":"13 and up."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this unit heats up ?","answer":"I haven't found that to be the case."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are they multiple games that can be played by more than 1 VR headset at a time and interest with both headsets at once...I.e. more than 1 player?","answer":"There are multiplayer online games and co-op games"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you watch movies with this?","answer":"Yes absolutely and very cool. I love it a great product. Finally, VR that you don't get dizzy."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I play purchaced games for the rift that are playable on the Quest without re purchaceing them?","answer":"If you have a supported graphics card you can with the new System link feature. It requires a USB C cord to connect it until the official fiber optic cable is released"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Wander App works on this device?","answer":"Yes, the Wander app is available for the Quest! You can see what apps are available for the Quest on our website here https://www.oculus.com/experiences/quest"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I need to buy a usb c to micro sd adapter for watching videos and movies?","answer":"No it’s all on there. That’s why we went for this system."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can this be synced to a steering wheel for driving games?","answer":"I don’t think so"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How many mAH is the battery","answer":"Fujian YU10850 18001A with capacity 3.85V / 3648 mAh (14.0 Wh), 2-3 hour life."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you play the new five nights at Freddy’s game on this?","answer":"No.  This title has not been released for the Oculus Quest."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the one lithium battery for ?","answer":"“ The Oculus Quest all in one virtual reality headset covered by this document contains a 3648mAh rechargeable lithium ion battery pack with a 14 watt-hour rating that powers the product. It is a double cell battery with a nominal voltage of 3.6 volts and it weighs approximatively 70 grams.”"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i connect this to my pc in the same way as a standard oculus, in addition to standalone play?","answer":"Hey, it's now possible to set the Quest up with your PC. Setup information can be found at https://support.oculus.com/525406631321134/#setup, while information for compatibility can be found at https://support.oculus.com/444256562873335/."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Save 44%? How can I get this discount?","answer":"Subscribe"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I need a play station like a ps4 to connect this with in order for it to work?","answer":"No it is a stand alone unit and does not require a ps4 for it to work. You would just need to download to Oculus app onto your phone to set it up and that's all. Wifi is needed for it to work"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Como descarg  los juegos en oculus","answer":"Los puedes descargar desde tu celular o desde Oculus (men  de los lentes) Hay un store, donde f cilmente puedes comprar y descargar. En el caso del celular lo mismo.  Es muy simple"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Now quest offers link to pc, pc i7-3770k, 16gb ram, gpu gtx980, especially the gpu, is that enough to run it smoothly, without lag? thnx in advance :)","answer":"Currently, the i7-3770k and GTX 980 don't meet the requirements for Oculus Link. Oculus Link is still currently in beta and we hope to add support for additional graphic cards by the end of the beta period. More information about Oculus Link compatibility is available here https://support.oculus.com/444256562873335/."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i want to give my nephew a gift card to buy games for his new oculus quest should i get one for the apple app store?","answer":"No. The Oculus Quest uses its own app store, which can be accessed via the Oculus app."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I bought this for my son for christmas, How/where to I get games, and can they be purchased ahead of time for his device? do I set it up before?","answer":"I bought this for my son also. He purchases games from within the system after set up. You will download all the games from my understanding.  The setup is done by pairing with his phone or tablet."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it run Minecraft with shaders ?","answer":"You could maybe run Minecraft mobile by sideloading. it's not in the Oculus store"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there further payments for shipping or import fee if i want to receive this item in Egypt ?","answer":"That's a question for amazon, not for people reviewing the product itself."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the quest compatible with a steering wheel for iracing?","answer":"Never tried it but the Quest gives the user VR hands, so its reasonable that they provide opportunity to use them..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i play Minecraft on this?","answer":"Yes you can play the windows 10 version of Minecraft with the Oculus Link cable that plugs the Quest into your computer. They are also working on a version specifically for the Quest I believe"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use Tilt Brush with this new oculus or do i still need a computer?","answer":"No you dont need a computer it has Tilt Brush in its Quest version of the Oculus store  ."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How many games can we expect by the end of the year","answer":"It has been stated that the Oculus Quest is on track for 100+ games by the end of the year on the official stores. There are also a lot of unofficial games that can be sideloaded, webvr, videos and films, and developer apps. It has a lot of content in ecosystems that are not officially supported. Official games are very immersive and fun, the unofficial games are sometimes impressive, sometimes not."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will  the device work over glasses?","answer":"It works well over glasses. Includes a spacer insert that goes between the facial interface and the headset to ensure enough room for glasses."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you buy more gigabytes for the quest if you got the 64 one?","answer":"You can't add additional storage to the 64GB version of the Quest."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you record gameplay with this?","answer":"It has a USB-C connection, but no other outlets to go to a recording station like a PC or capture card."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do you screen share to tv and does it cast audio as well?","answer":"You can screen cast through Chromecast but it doesn't work with TVs which have built-in chromecast."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are there any world war two flying games ??","answer":"I have not come across any I don’t think, but still a great purchase"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the device work  and adapter in 220v ?  , is it ok to charge with other adapter and cable? (Like similar phone charger (usb   usb-c cable)?","answer":"No, the product does not operate at 220 volts. Similiar chargers, etc void your warranty....."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this play no man sky ?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there any protection plan available for this?  Best Buy offers one but I want to know if amazon does too.","answer":"Amazon has a warranty, i purchased a padded case for product protection..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do i need a smart phone i have a samsung tablet a gaming pc and a samsung 55 inch 4k tv but my my phone is one of those free insurance phones?","answer":"You can use the Oculus app on any phone running Android 6.0 or higher or iOS 10 or higher. The phone also needs to be connected to Wi-Fi and have Bluetooth turned on to setup your Quest. You may be able to get it to work with your tablet but there is no guarantee."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long does it take to arrive?","answer":"It depends on if it’s in stock or if you have prime"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the come with Oculus warranty?","answer":"yes, if you buy now."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are you able to play Tiny Town with the Quest?","answer":"You can play Steam VR games on your PC and use Virtual Desktop or similar sideloaded streaming app to view them through the Quest headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is this headset compatible with xbox 1S or above?","answer":"No. It is a stand alone headset. Or, you also can play Steam games from a pc by using the Oculus Link Cable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this product come with Bluetooth or headphone jack support?","answer":"It supports headphone jack but no Bluetooth. You don’t want that latency to cause you motion sickness anyway."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What gpu does it have?","answer":"For Gaming, it has to be very high or high enough but for virtual desktop or Bigscreen you can you basic GPU"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i order now, when can i get it? i need it before 15th jul (chicago)","answer":"This question is better directed at Oculus or FB, as they have the logistics..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this oculus rift come with everything needed for beginners including the cameras?","answer":"This is NOT the Oculus Rift. This is the Oculus Quest. Completely different products."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hi everyone, if i purchase this do i need to buy anything else to start playing as computer or wires, games? What is add cost.?","answer":"You need a compatible smartphone to do the initial setup. It comes with 5 demos pre-loaded and there are a number apps that you can purchase with varying prices."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use the same controllers for the oculus gear?","answer":"These controllers only work with the Oculus Quest and or Oculus Rift S. They are designed for  Inside Out Tracking ". Cameras built into the Quest and S track these controllers eliminating the need for external tracking hardware. The Oculus Gear doesn't have this capability to track. It is an older system.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with Space Engine?","answer":"What is the space engine ?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are there any taxes?","answer":"It’s after January 1st not sure of law, but I don’t think we paid any"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"this is working in israel ?","answer":"Works anywhere"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it fit apple iPhone xr","answer":"This is not a headset to insert a phone or device. It is a complete system and you download games and apps directly onto it."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why is it more expensive than the oculus website?","answer":"Because different businesses purchase it at regular price and attempt to turn a profit."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it connect with Bluetooth?","answer":"Yes it does. You will need to connect your Oculus Quest to your smartphone the first time you set it up. You can also stream what you see on the quest to your smartphone using wifi."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"So you dont need a pc to use this?","answer":"That's right, you don't need a PC to use it! You do need a smartphone to do the initial set up."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"128GB order with 1st minute, so free games ?","answer":"Just basic games to get started. You order more from menu inside the h"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If I wanted to use this in more than 1 room do I have to set the play area up each time or will it remember different play areas for different rooms?","answer":"HI, not sure, only using in one room. But setting up play area takes less than a minute and is very intuitive"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I play vr chat?","answer":"Yup"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are there any anatomy games","answer":"Yes there is one on the quest and one on the quest go you can download games on the quest go to your quest"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you connect wireless headphones/earbuds instead?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you plug in headphones","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the Shipping weight?","answer":"5.7 lbs via UPS"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If running game from moblie, so 64gb or 128gb for what?","answer":"Sir/ Madam: CAPACITY! You can store more games, etc. It would save you having to delete some, down the road. Your purchased apps are yours and you could reinstall them later, if so desired, “I love my 128gb Quest!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Would like to purchase this item from spain. the currency exchange will be done from actual $499 to euros? i mean, would i pay  499, or about  452?","answer":"I paid $540USD  for this. Worth it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why is the price so high compared to the actual website that sells this for 499.00? Let’s be reasonable","answer":"Memory, you can save$100 by finding one with less memory. The 128GB I couldnt find less than $500. Hot tip......get the 128GB, you will be glad you did."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this headset work on Steam?","answer":"Not directly, but you can use Virtual Desktop to stream Steam games to the headset. In this config, the Quest provides display and control (if required) but the heavy lifting for running the game is done by the PC."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it possible to watch regular (non VR) videos in it? If yes, then how?","answer":"You can watch videos, but they’re not VR."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with a system that will allow audience, not using vr, to watch the action? If so, what gaming system works best?","answer":"Yes it is.  I know that you have to get another piece of hardware which would then link up to a specified device via Bluetooth.  I don’t remember what that hardware is but it’s easily available."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why there's free shipping on the 64 and not on 128????","answer":"When I bought it there was free shipping. You’d have to ask amazon"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I know it said on one of the amazon banners that the oculus quest 128gb version will cost $499. Is this true please respond quickly?","answer":"No, your eyes are lying to you. The Oculus only costs 4 cupcakes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I trade in my rift towards this model?","answer":"It depends on the model"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"why is the tax 41.42 on amazon but only 31.44 on walmart? tax is tax. is this a scam?","answer":"Tax differs depending on your shipping location. Some local governments impose higher tax than others."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the charge life for headset?","answer":"2.5 hrs. I'd recommend an external battery if your worried."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use this to play my steamvr games i have on steam?","answer":"If you download SyQuest there is some games you can play on your quest. But be careful some of the side roads mess up your gaming system"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"why double a batteries are included?","answer":"For the hand controllers.  love this VR set"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"In what ways does this oculus quest compare and differ from the oculus rift?","answer":"With the new Oculus Link update which just came out, you are able to connect the Quest to a PC and play essentially all the same games the Rift can play, plus the Quest exclusives  as well as having the ability to simply unplug and go to a friends house or wherever you want really, and have a fun VR experience. I'd say the biggest difference now is tracking the controllers,  but it's never been a very big issue for me personally. In my opinion,  the quest is an absolute must have even if you  just like VR a little bit. On the technical side the Rift has a slightly faster refresh rate but it's almost impossible to notice,  while the Quest has better resolution. But again the difference is there but I doubt most people would notice the difference that much."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How fast did you get it?","answer":"A few days"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does Amazon offer a warranty for this product?","answer":"Not that I believe"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i'm ordering to the russian federation, which shipping company is handling the package? can i deliver to the company's pickup point?","answer":"That would probably be  UPS or FedX " If it is allowed you can do that.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will the quest play rift games?","answer":"The Quest doesn't play Rift games but there are Quest versions of Rift games and in many cases, the developers have made the Quest version free if you already purchased the Rift version."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Mine in december. expected ship date was the second week of january. why was my order canceled","answer":"Sold out, back in stock soon"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do l have to pay custom charges on this if sent to the uk?","answer":"Before final purchase via Amazon it should provide a breakdown of charges vat customers etc along with the retail price. Should give you a better indication before completing your purchase"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can Oculus quest be used on an I phone 6?","answer":"As long as you can install the Oculus app, yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for android?","answer":"It does work with Android"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What other extras do you need to purchase that are not included in the box for this VR to be operational other than games?","answer":"Everything you need to experience Virtual Reality comes in the box for the Quest. This is a stand alone system. It is software driven and will need to be connected to a WIFI system in your home in order to download software apps and having a smart phone for the initial setup too. That being said, it is an amazing experience to be able to watch Netflix on a 200 inch screen sitting in a ski lodge while sitting in your small apartment living room or bedroom. Or watching a movie on an Imax size movie screen sharing with a friend who also owns a Quest. Or fight Darth Vader with a light-saber while using the force. :-)"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is storage expandable through sd card or anything, or only 128gb?","answer":"No SD card slot"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How does the headstrap work?","answer":"Adjustable and easy to use.  Works for all size heads."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use a iphone xr to set it up","answer":"Yes, just download the Oculus app from the App Store."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this be used while charging/plugged in (like Samsung VR)?","answer":"Sure with a 3A output powerbank it will work perfect"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the release date the shipping date?","answer":"No, release date is when the product is available, shipping is some time after your purchase...."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Could I buy more storage later","answer":"No."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do i redeem the vader immortal offer? i read (here) that there is supposed to be a code. where i do i find this code?","answer":"If you purchased and activated a new Quest headset between November 21, 2019 and January 21, 2020, the Vader Immortal bundle should be added automatically to your Oculus account. There isn't a separate code. If the Vader Immortal bundle hasn't been added to your account, please contact support at https://support.oculus.com."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this unit need a wifi internet signal to work?","answer":"To purchase and download games, not to play already purchased games."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will preordering it guarantee ill get it on the 21st?","answer":"No, unless it is qualified, during purchase, pre ordering only confirms your purchase"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How easy would it be to watch videos (YT, Netflix, etc) and navigating, while lying flat on a bed?","answer":"This works well in a lighted room.  Each app has its own method to reorient the screen to be above you in your line of sight while lying down.  Usually, you hold down the recessed Oculus button while looking in the direction that you want the screen to be placed.  Some apps will have you reorient the screen by dragging it to the desired location.  The method varies, but it works quite well."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Se puede conectar con Xbox?","answer":"No, el Oculus Quest est  dise ado para trabajar de manera independiente. De forma est ndar no se conecta ni al pc ni al Xbox. Puede que haya alguna soluci n parche pero no es natural"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with Xbox one","answer":"I don’t know my grandson loves both of them."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i ride around with this on a atv?","answer":"Virtually, yes. Real world no!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I need a computer or phone to use this or can I use it just by wearing the headset?","answer":"When you set the game up I believe I needed the phone but after that you do not need your phone for set up"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the headset and/or browser have parental controls? Can you lock down or delete the web browser?","answer":"As far as I can tell the Quest currently does not have parental controls on the default apps. That being said, you can easily set up the Quest to stream to the phone it is connected to via the Oculus App, this allows you to see/hear everything the headset sees."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hi      Iordered this item.  Can i get  this one before sunday?","answer":"It depends if they have it in stock"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what us resolution (6K) and can you download VR material from online to play?","answer":"Resolution is very high quality.  6K does not relevant.  Yes you download from on-line store"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"We have to charge the vr headset, right? how much time? how long will a fully charged vr headset last?","answer":"A full charge lasts around 2 - 3 hours of use. Takes around 2 hrs to fully charge from 0."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you need a ps4 to use this product ?","answer":"No. You don’t need anything else."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Yes, why are you trying to sell this for $634 when the 128G  is sold at the manufacturer for only $499?","answer":"From my understanding the oculus quest is offered from many different companies. And for many different prices. I paid a high price for mine because I wanted to get one as soon as I could . I bought four of the at one time. Many companies limit how many they will sell at one time."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i voice chat?","answer":"Yes! You absolutely can ! You can chat in the Gabe you are playing or you can do a party chat"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you insert the phone in the headset?","answer":"No phone inside for a screen. It is just like the PC vr headsets and has everything you need in it. You only need a phone to pair and boot the headset with the oculus app."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Who can i contact about the vader free games offer? ordered on 12/30 but quest won't arrive until feb which is past 30 day activation window...","answer":"It goes by your purchase date.  I believe either 31 Dec or 1 Jan 2020 was the cutoff for the free Vader game. I might be incorrect.  Go to the Oculus website and send them a email."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I get next day delivery","answer":"Sure, but the shipping costs much"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I have to change the batteries or I can recharge them?","answer":"The headset battery can not be changed, it's rechargeable. But the controllers require AA batteries. You can always buy AA rechargeable batteries."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are games that are purchased on the oculus go available on the oculus quest?","answer":"...there is some cross over but not much...if you bought certain apps and games on the Oculus Go there is a select option to Go or Quest titles and install on the Quest..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I’m a trucker and the idea of being able to wear a TV on my face appeals to me as opposed to holding an iPad, would the Quest work well for this?","answer":"My son says it’s “cool” to watch YouTube videos that way."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will the headset fit kids ?","answer":"My grandkids heave no problems as early as 3 years old"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why is this unit priced at $499 while another from Oculus is listed at $666. Is there any difference?","answer":"My son said the $666 price might be for a bundle (including games) but you would need to check with Oculus to verify that.  Otherwise there is not an upgraded model."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the oculus quest a good Christmas present","answer":"Absolutely! My mother is 68 and had a lot of fun catching fish in the game  Bait " and my 15byear old son loved the action games. It really is good for all ages, as well as being good for entry level VR users and more experienced VR users at the same time!""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i pay for the extra money for shiping will it ship faster or the amount i pay for or the same amount of time?","answer":"Enterprises LLC has this item in stock and shipping out same day or next business day using USPS Priority shipping.  Upgraded shipping may cut 1-2 days off delivery depending on what part of the country your in and carrier’s able to meet the expected deliver by date at the time of the order. This response is seller specific to us."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with the link cable?","answer":"The Quest comes with a charging cable. The link cable is used to connect the Quest your PC and must be purchased separately."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you watch Netflix? iTunes?","answer":"Yes, you can watch Netflix on the Quest! There is no iTunes app available for the Quest though."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with a microphone?","answer":"Yes it comes with a built-in mic"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with google world vr?","answer":"It will work with any VR compatiple software but i am confident that the Google software, or some variation will work....."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Funciona app con motorola g6??","answer":"No entiendo mucho tu pregunta porque el Quest es un equipo independiente. Pero si te refieres al uso de internet compartido con el mobil: en teror a deber a funcionar. Yo lo he probado con mi mobil (que no es un g6) y a funcionado sin problemas. Si puedes compartir el internet a traves el g6 con una computadora usando wifi creo que no deber as tener problemas con el QUEST"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Our volume/sound quick working, is there a setting?","answer":"There is buttons on the bottom to turn sound up and down"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Multiple users?","answer":"Currently, the Quest supports the use of one account at a time."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use the headset as just a monitor?","answer":"You can play the games without plug in to console or PC. Is wireless.."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it play games from steam be?","answer":"Yes, you can! While Quest is a standalone VR headset. With a compatible PC and appropriate USB 3.0 cable, you can also use the Oculus Link feature to connect it to a PC to play Rift PC games."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it have a micro SD slot to add extra memory?","answer":"Nope!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"The audio on mine crackles occasionally on the left side. Is there a way to fix this?","answer":"Hey, does this persist regardless of the audio volume? Is there any change when you try using the headphone ports? Create a ticket at https://support.oculus.com, we're more than happy to identify the cause, and look to assist if possible."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you need headphones or a headset?","answer":"The headset has built in speakers so you don't have to use headphones and the sound actually comes through quite well (feels immersive to the player), but it also means that anyone around you can hear what you're hearing as well. The headset has headphone jacks so you can plug in your own if you want to be the only one hearing the sound."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If it breaks where do I send it?","answer":"If you're having issues with your headset, please contact support at https://support.oculus.com."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What ports are on the headset?","answer":"L/R audio and a charging port."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is this much better than the oculus go?","answer":"If you are looking for 360 degree game immersion, the Quest has it with dual controllers and the ability to map out a safe play area. So big upgrade for gaming."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you watch nba?","answer":"Yes, you can watch NBA games with League Pass.  You can also watch certain games after they have been played for free.  I believe it takes a couple days to post."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"So just what kind of games can i play? beatsaber or bioshock 2 level? if this could run last gen fps games i'm all over it.","answer":"Just beat saber"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I’m new to this please forget this question, do you have to buy a gaming console or anything else with these? How do you play the games?","answer":"This is a stand-alone product, and the first like this from the Oculus brand. I would encourage you to watch some youtube videos about its functionality. Games are downloaded via wifi and can be purchased or searched through the Oculus app on your smartphone."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do we buy more games for occulus all in one vr? Do we buy and store them on our space or do we stream them ? And where can see the pricing for it","answer":"You download their app on your phone and purchase them there or through the headset. The games download onto the units memory, but are held in your library to download again if needed"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I know it comes with a insert for people with glasses, how is the comfort while wearing glasses though?","answer":"The comfort level is okay, but what I did was order lenses with my prescription from WidmoVR.  Rx lenses are so much better than wearing glasses.  Also, if you’re use your Quest to exercise then I recommend getting Quick Spit from Amazon.  The Quick Spit will keep your lenses from fogging.  The way I use the Spit is, first I clean the lens , then spray Spit onto the lens, rub it into the lens and leave it for a few minutes, remove the Spit with a microfiber cloth and enjoy a fog-free workout."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I bought it at wanna bring it on a plane but it said on the amazon box that i couldnt bring on a plane is that true?","answer":"I'd say No, if that is what it said on the packaging"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this the new and original oculus quest 128 gb?  Why does it says Vogek?","answer":"Probably sold by a 3rd party vendor"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this product have warranty through manufacturer?","answer":"Yes, there is a warranty through the manufacturer! Our warranty terms are available here https://www.oculus.com/legal/limited-warranty/"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this a good fit for a 11 year old boy?","answer":"My son has had the oculus rift since he was 8 and loves it. He’s 11 now and we plan to get this for him for Christmas. Fit never seemed to be an issue."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Y como puedo poner dinero en oculus","answer":"Amazon no me entrego el Oculus Quest, en su lugar llego un Lego"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you watch vudu or movies anywhere via the quest?","answer":"You can use the quest as a wirelessly connected computer monitor.  This requires that the quest have wifi access to a network that your computer is exposed to.  However,  there are shows I watch on cable that I can't stream to my computer and hence can't watch on quest.  It is a small list these days though as most programming is available to computer devices via one avenue or another.  The real limitation is the wifi connectivity between computer and quest.  If your computer is at home and you're at a Starbucks,  you'll need additional setup ahead of time to access your home computer via Starbucks wifi connection - that setup is do-able but is independent of the Quest."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I play Minecraft on this","answer":"You will have to google it, I have older children 16  they play beat saber, boxing and another one, if it’s available for game it’s a in app purchase."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use oculus go apps on the Quest?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How much memory does a game use?","answer":"Not very much, in the 10's of Mbs. Which is why most games are very basic with even more simple graphics. There was alot of hype around this system, in my opinion the games are fun but lose the wow factor very quickly"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How much on average  are the games?","answer":"Anywhere from free to $30. Most of the good games are $15-$25. The Vader Immortal is $10 for each episode."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"with a 128 gb how many games can you download?","answer":"128 gb worth of games. Good question."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hola quiero comprar Oculus Rift S, para cuando estaria disponible","answer":"Yo soy de chile y se demoro muy poco en llegar lo compre el 9 y lleguo el 17"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I bought this before 1/31. how do i redeem the 3 episodes of the star wars game?","answer":"If you purchased within the promotional period then the Vader Immortal content should be automatically added to first Oculus account used to setup your Oculus Quest. If you're not seeing in the Library, please contact support here https://support.oculus.com/885981024820727/ so we can look into this for you. Thanks!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"The sound is distorted on the right external speaker. works fine with buds but for $500 i'd prefer 100% working hardware. any ideas before i return?","answer":"Yeah, return it quickly so they aren't sold out. Ooops, you may have missed that window."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Where can you browse the games before dropping 400-500 on this thing?","answer":"In Oculus store"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with Samsung notebook 8","answer":"Hi! We sent an inquiry to the manufacturer but it will take 24-48 hours to get a response. However the description of this items says it can be use with (6.0 Marshmallow or higher) smartphone and can stand alone VR that no PC required. Hope this helps"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I refuse to over pay, When will Amazon have more in stock at legit prices ??","answer":"Daily. Just keep checking back."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I’m in a wheelchair and can’t walk. will this affect my ability to realize the full potential of vr? will this be a good item for use if i can’t walk?","answer":"Very little walking required. I believe it would be wonderful to experience."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How can I get movies/games from website? Would you share some links that I can download? thanks.","answer":"Most content is obtained through the official store, no need for external eebditrs or software. You can, however, use a sideloader to downloaf other content."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work in abu dhabi, uae?  a lot of things are blocked over here.  tia","answer":"I don't know. I live in New Jersey but it should. Good luck"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Puedo ver peliculas 3d?","answer":"Hola Juan no tuve la chance de probar ese formato. En cuanto lo pruebe mi equipo de software te aviso, mail es info@accelone.com acordate asi me preguntas. M"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why did my oculus come with a uk adapter when it shows the us adapter is included?","answer":"If you ordered in the United State, it should have come with us adapter."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the headset and/or browser have parental controls? Can you lock down or delete the web browser?","answer":"The Quest currently doesn't have parental controls available and it isn't possible to delete the web browser."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what happen to the oculus quest 128GB for 499.00 which is what i wanted purchase   it went up 300.00 in a matter of a few minutes?","answer":"Just keep checking and make sure it’s from amazon not third party"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you play beat saber","answer":"Yes My Favorist game"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What's the storage for? My Vive saves things to my computer...","answer":"The storage is so you don't have to save things to a computer. So if you want to travel with the quest you can play your Media off line."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I know this does not require a computer to play. But can I use a computer or console if i wanted to?","answer":"The recent updates promised support for so called Oculus Link, which should enable you to connect it to PC with the supplied cable and play as if your were using Oculus Rift. Haven't tried it yet, so am not sure if it's implemented yet."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a virtual drum set game available on the Quest?","answer":"nope"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is storage expandable through sd card or anything, or only 128gb?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Gaming is great but what other kind of apps can you use 6dof? Can you use travel apps like Wander or 360?","answer":"Checkout the Oculus store to see what's available. In addition, you can use YouTube VR and the like."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Cu nto tiempo dura la bateria","answer":"Eso depende mucho del uso que le des, procre  que una hora estar a en promedio. De todas formas (aunque depende de cada quien) estos equipos VR no son para un uso constante porque producen fatiga y es bueno descartar de a ratos"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you transfer the visual of the vr to the TV?","answer":"I believe if you have a tv that supports chrome cast you can"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use my wireless bluetotth head phones for sound with game?","answer":"My son doesn’t think you can. He uses his wired headset that he uses for his xbox"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How many games come with the headset when you purchase it?  And how much do extra games cost?","answer":"Only a demo on how to use it, no games  Some games are free, all others are about 3-40$, but there are a lot of sales and demos"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When is release","answer":"It's out"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i want to stream a movie do both of us need a pc","answer":"You don't need a PC if you are using the Netflix or YouTube apps from the Oculus store. If you have a Google Play  account you can syn it to your YouTube account and you can stream movies you bought on Google Play. Which is a nice bonus, and you can make it a curved screen making it like being at the movies."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are you sure about the January stock date?","answer":"I ordered mine with a stock date nearly 4 weeks out, but within two days it had been stocked and I had it within a week. I don't think they are sure of any of the dates, but they seem to be trying to avoid angering people by estimating on the long side, which is good. I was very happy to get mine 3 weeks early."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this the virtual system i can use to play half life alyx in march 2020?","answer":"The Oculus Quest can now be connected to a PC to play games such as Half Life, but I don’t think there are currently plans for a Quest native version."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hello we have to exchange this because the screen resolution is blurry but we bought $75 worth of games already? Do we get them back?","answer":"Hey, games should be tied to the account that had purchased them. If you have trouble accessing them, reach out to our Support and we can work with you to resolve it."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What games can you get 128GB","answer":"Oculus has a store that divides games by device Go/Quest/Rift.  Quest games are best, but if you already owned a Go game and didn’t want to re-buy it you could play on Quest.     Beta feature could let you connect a Quest to a computer and play some Rift games.  Frame rate and stability of those games is probably going to be lower, but a nice option to have.     In general, 128GB seems to hold the majority of the Quest game catalog.  I haven’t had to delete anything yet and have dozens of games/apps."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it run app purchase from Rift","answer":"Yes, but not everything is available on the quest, for example if you bought robo recall you can use it on the quest"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it prevent you from storing games on external memory via its usb like the Oculus Go does?","answer":"No external saving yet"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What options are there to cast to tv? Most other answers are old. Have they added other capabilities in the last year?","answer":"It’s still not available."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you play Minecraft?","answer":"Officially, not yet unfortunately. There’s a way to sideload it but I haven’t tried that and can’t speak to how good it is or how difficult."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this item be returned if opened after I use it?","answer":"I think you have 30 days to return to Amazon, you just give reason, if you live near Kohl’s most are a drop off spot otherwise you can print off label, you can chat in app with a Amazon Rep"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the game included in the oculus? Or do we need to buy it seperatly with an app or sth?","answer":"It comes with a few free titles and some demos but you need to buy most of the real games. They mostly range from $9.99 to $29.99.  Robo Recall, Beat Saber and Superhot are must-have titles."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this product work with a samsung s10+? i had the oculus go and the phone would not connect to the headset. yes, i did all the trouble shooting. c","answer":"You just download an app, oculus app you don’t really need your phone after set up it’s wireless and it’s own “console”"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will an iphone 7 work for this, or am i going to have to get a new phone?  can i use a laptop instead of an iphone?","answer":"You just need a fairly modern iPhone or Android phone to configure the device.  An iPhone 7 should be just fine. After the initial setup you don’t really need the phone as most things can be done on the Quest itself."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what's means  for 6640-906-105 "?"","answer":"It pertains to the model no. If The Headset and it's function with lynks by microsoft"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what comes in the box?","answer":"The headset, two additional ear pieces, computer USB adapter, a 1 ft. mini-USB cable for charging, which you can connect directly to the earpiece or the box itself for charging when the headset is in the cradle as pictured."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I answer skype calls from the headset with the answer call button?","answer":"Yes, I believe you can."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hi!I see the customer announced that they had to have the problems 2-4 months after use! For for how the month we have the waranty or guaranteed pls?","answer":"There is a white paper that comes with the Jabra that says Limited One (1) year warranty. for the first end user  purchasing the product from a distributor or reseller.  that the product shall be free from defects in materials and workmanship subject to the terms set forth. Specifically exempt from warranty are limited-life consumable components and accessories subject to normal wear and tear. For a complete overview of which consumable components and accessories that are not covered by this Warranty, Please go to www.jabra.com  you can see everything about the warranty there."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does closing the boom turn off the headset?","answer":"yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this pair with 2 bluetooth devices at once? I want to use w/laptop and cell phone together and easily switch between them.","answer":"I currently use it with 2 mobile phones and it works well. I haven't tried it with a PC yet."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this headset be worn on either side ear?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hi!is there any warranty or  guarantee  for this Article?For how much time?","answer":"I sell it independently.  Keep receipt Jabba offers 1 year on it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I answer skype calls from the headset with the answer call button?","answer":"Yes as long as your phone is paired.  Also you can have your skype forwarded to your phone so it can be picked up by your paired device also."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How heavy/sturdy is the base station on a desk?  Does it feel solid?","answer":"It is fine on the desk.  The base also holds a USB cable if you'd prefer to attach it to your PC"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the difference between uc and uc+","answer":"I didn't have a chance to find out, and my head set is dead, and not long my other set is not function anymore too. Very disappointed after spending high price for that junks."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use this product while it is charging?","answer":"The base is the charger  so no"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Jabra MOTION UC with Travel and Charge Kit  come with the warranty from Jabra?","answer":"It works very well I was hoping the fit was better."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"mute button not work good      when i pair it with my sony xperia z1 frequent message on mobile say  not supported contact sony or change headset  ?","answer":"Perhaps, Experia needs a software update?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with Cisco Jabber?","answer":"Yes, it works with Cisco UC Jabber"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what's in the box","answer":"J.C.B. below is the package contents. Package Contents: MOTION UC Earset, Link 360 Bluetooth USB Adaptor, Travel & Charge Case, 3 x Sizes of Ear Gels, USB Cable, USB Wall Charger"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long does the battery last? At times I can be on the phone for 8 hours a day. I need both comfort and longevity.","answer":"I'd buy two.. You may get that long with a new headset, but after 6 months, I think you'd be lucky to get 2-3 hours call time."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the difference between the Motion UC and Jarbra Motion mono?","answer":"In my opinion, the UC is more versatile, due to the fact that it has the usb to connect to my PC."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I am willing to order this article but I am afraid it is not compatible with my iphone or laptop hp, can you tell me please? otherwise, what does it m","answer":"I use it with my iPhone and it works great! I have a Mac, but as long as your laptop is bluetooth compatible it should work seemlessly as well."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can it switch from right ear to left ear easily","answer":"Yes, the ear piece swivels for wearing in either ear. Mine has held up well to almost daily use. Currently on my second one in about 4 years only because I washed my first one. It still worked for a while even after going through both the washer and dryer! Great product!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how does it work/feel with eyeglasses and sunglasses ?","answer":"Of course will depend on your frames, but half our office wear glasses and nobody noticed any discomfort, there is a surprising amount of adjustability and the attachment around the ear is all very flexible."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what is the pixal resolution per eye.  Im guessing that because it is not stated its not very high.","answer":"Thanks for your questions,we suggest you take one have a try and test.  We uses advanced Micro-OLED displays which has over 3000PPI (Pixels per inch), delivering dual 1920 1080 resolution, ultra-high contrast ratio, and blistering fast image response time. The display pairs the deep black and natural color of OLED for enhanced color contrast. Everything you watch comes to life with fine detail and vivid color."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do you listen?","answer":"There are two ways to listen:  1) Using the 3.5mm wired earphone to connect with the vr headset.  2)Using the bluetooth earphone to connect with the controller.  Please note you need an extra earphone to enjoy this VR headset, not included in package."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this support VR?","answer":"Yes, it is VR compatible. You are able to watch 3D videos and play VR Games."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What color is the actual headset? Its shows green here but in my orders page it shows blue","answer":"Mine came blue."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use this for ps vita?","answer":"Yes it has a stero headphone jack"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Would these headphones work with other brands of corded office phone with built in 2.5 mm headphone jack? ie. Panasonic.","answer":"It works great with any type of phone"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it cancel out background noise when you're not talking/when the person on the other line is talking?","answer":"The people I talk with never complain that there is background noise.  They always hear me clearly."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will Android headsets work with this adapter?  Does both the earphones and microphone work with it?","answer":"Yes, Android headsets will work with this adapter, and both the earphones and microphone will work. But pls note that this adapter only works with some specific phones, only buy the item if you have one of the phone or amplifier models listed in description."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I love the look of this headset, i've had another one from this company too, they're super comfy. does it come with the pc cable?","answer":"yes, it has"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When I plug the  headset to my laptop I can’t hear anything","answer":"Mine was pretty much plug and play, I might look for some driver settings? If you know how to do that..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have an older xbox one controller which needs an adapter. What type of adapter do i need to get?","answer":"Not sure my was plug and pkay"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How does the mic work? is it vox? does it cancel out ambient noise and only react to your voice when talking across the game?","answer":"there is a swtch and 3.5mm for the MIC. PLEASE CHECK"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the mic bendable ?","answer":"Yes it is"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can someone respond i have two if these now and can not figure out how to make them work. it’s an xbx one. do i need the hdmi port adapter?","answer":"the headset work on the new xbox one. if you are the old edition xhox one, you need an adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these work with Nintendo switch?","answer":"Yes. There's a standard headphone jack that you can plug into"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is the cord to plug in a controller?","answer":"it is about 2meters"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"It worked and then it stopped, Is their a guide to trouble shooting? I am not getting the voice, sound, or lights to work.","answer":"thank you so mcuh for your atttention. can you adjust the mic phone switch and then if you have anyohter question, please let me know and we will make refund and replacement for u."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"skype for business compatible?","answer":"Microsoft Lync compatible"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for PlayStation 4","answer":"Yes. It will work wirelessly with the PS4 out of the box."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will these work with the new xbox one controllers with the 3.55 jacks ?  can i use them to chat without the headset adapter ?","answer":"I believe you would have to purchase a 2.5 adapter to 3.55 but I am not certain. I'm sorry I personally never used mine."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will there have somthing come out so it works with the xbox one","answer":"They work with the xbox one u have to buy a xbox one headset adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"good day, would ask for a headset ship. deliver it even after germay so internationally. and what would the shipping cost? thank you for your trouble","answer":"you can estimate the shipping from the cart before you buy them"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"it shows xbox 360.  Does it work for ps3 as well?","answer":"Yes it does.."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you conect it to a ps3","answer":"Yes you can. Just the same way with the ps4"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have had this headset for almost a year now, but all of a sudden i cannot talk through my mic, is something broken??","answer":"Check your headset controls.  Update console AND the headset by going to Turtle Beach website."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does the voice morph work on PS4???","answer":"by default, no.  Is supposed to need an update to allow PS4 support, but I bricked 2 doing the update.  I would not recommend buying"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these comfortable with glasses and long sessions of gaming?","answer":"Depends on your glasses, if the sides are wide and thick they will hurt However if they're thin and small not so much."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"IT WORK FOR PC","answer":"Although not officially supported for PC use, you may be able to use it depending on your system's configuration. Additional information and details can be found in our Knowledgebase: http://support.turtlebeach.com/entry/830517212/"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this have the same problem as the Ear Force Tango where the headphone power down because it thinks there is no audio (even when there is)?","answer":"mine only power off wen there not been used"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Out of the box with his work for Xbox one?","answer":"No.  I would suggest the Turtle Beach website for all your information needs!  The have all the headsets and have them broken down by gamer type, price, console, etc.  And then they list all the system requirements, hook-up flow charts, technical specs."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"The bluetoothe adapter doesn't fit in the microsoft stereo adapter for xbox one. how do you connect the adapter to the controller?","answer":"Im almost certain there's no way to connect to the xbox one controller wirelessly. You'll have to use the cable provided to chat."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How/where do I get voice morph presets for this headset?","answer":"You can find them on the turtle beach website under their 'community presets' tab. Just search for the phantom headset, though i believe preset tabs for other headsets will work. Heres a link   http://www.turtlebeach.com/community/preset-community"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do i use this headset with my xbox one?","answer":"Instructions on connecting the Phantom headset to your Xbox One console may be found here: https://support.turtlebeach.com/hc/en-us/articles/224121507-Phantom-Xbox-One-Setup-Diagram"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What cables do I need if I want them to work on ps4","answer":"None.  HOWEVER, you will need to go to turtlebeach.com and connect thg e headset to your computer (cables are all supplied)  to download the PS4 compatibility software.  You will also get a ton of really neat presets for the headset as well."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with OEM Box?","answer":"Mine did, factory sealed"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I need to replace the ear cups. Which one should I get?","answer":"I had to replaced them too. Go to turttlebeach.com and buy them from them. Theyre really cheap."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can this unit be substituted for comuter headset","answer":"You can connect via bluetooth, but to get the full use of the set, you'll want to connect to the optical port -- which means your computer (sound card) needs an optical out."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work on ps4","answer":"Yes! It work fine on ps4 :P"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a port mic jack wher I can plug my mp3 up to it and play music while I game..Thanks??","answer":"Yes. However the jack is also used to connect to the controller for in-game chat. So you have to choose between talking to friends or listening to music. If you have a 360, it comes with wireless chat. Btw, this headset is only truly wireless on X360. Other systems, you are tethered to the controller."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with ALL  original cables and accessories?","answer":"yes it does."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"IT WORK DOR PC","answer":"Works on PC using Digital Optical Output"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you need batories to power the headset","answer":"No it doesn't. They are. Built in and rechargeable. They last up to 15 hours on a full charge depending on how long you leave them on."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"My mic is not working. no one can hear me, and i can't hear myselfi did updates through turtle beach, my console, i've tried everything. what do i do?","answer":"Not sure if you've tried it yet, but I'd double check all my settings on the console. After I updated one time, one of my settings (mic output??) somehow got changed and no one could hear me."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use this headset on my PC for gaming?","answer":"To hook up the audio from sound card you can use 3.5mm jack to RCA cable or if your sound card has optical output you can use the fiber optics cable this headset does NOT SUPPORT SPDIF digital output audio. For chat i don't know for 100% but i thing you going to need Bluetooth sound output device. I found one online for $40 and decided it's not worth it because i don't need it as bad as to spend 40 bucks. so the chat can't tell but if your PC supports Bluetooth headphones or speakers and mic i don't see why not - it should work. Headset works excellent with my XBox360 and PS3 also my TV with optical output, also same time with my android smartphone. I can pair two devices at the same time on the Bluetooth. When I don't chat i can listen to the music from my phone while playing but you can only have one stream thru Bluetooth so if you chat you can't listen to music, when there is incoming phone call chat is interrupted and vice verse. In scale from 1 o 10 suiting my needs i give 10 i have also older set Black Ops Tango, which my son is using but none of us use it on PC. I just read another post true there is small 2.5mm receptacle on the headset but I was using it only wireless. Why spend $300 (that's what i paid)and still have wires dangling from the headset, when comparable sound quality can give $80 set?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work with xbox one","answer":"Diane, you would also need to purchase an Xbox One Headset Adapter made by Microsoft to use this with an Xbox One. With the adapter it willwork perfectly with the Xbox One."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with PS4","answer":"yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have had this this headsets over a year, suddenly base would not turn on at all. Is there a way to fix this? Can I buy just the base?","answer":"Same thing had happened to me after about 2 years. Just the way it goes. I was going to buy another base, but I believe they go for about 100 to 150 alone from turtle beach. Youre better just buying the whole thing new again."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"My transmitter stopped working. Plugged in.. wont turn on at all. Tried pairing with headset, no lights. Tried plugging in my comp.. wont work. Help?!","answer":"This is how my first pair went. The transmitter is more than likely dead at this point."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"are the mic very sensitive?? are the speakers loud? (loud as anybody in the room can hear the headset withow having it).","answer":"If by sensitive you mean if the mic picks up ambient noises from the background than no, not overly so. As for loud, no the speakers aren't loud enough to be heard by people not wearing the headset while you wear it. If no on is wearing it then there is some muffled spill out at med to high volume setting."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these have the same features as the XP510s?","answer":"Yes they do."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"So there is no wires","answer":"There is one, from the headset to the controller. It is not completely wireless as you are tethered to your controller."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"This or the Tangos?","answer":"They are actually pretty similar. The Phantom is newer and should have slightly better specifications, like the processor is much faster, but you are unlikely to notice too much difference. It may come down to which color scheme you prefer. They are both compatible with an Xbox One if you get an adapter, and with the PS4, but you need to purchase a talkback cable for the Tango while that cable comes with the Phantom. That is $17 you don't need to spend if you get the Phantom."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will these work with xbox one?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this headset compatible with other mobile devices?","answer":"Yes, but if you want to use Mic function, you had to buy a 2 to 1 adapter!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this be used with psp4","answer":"It can if you buy the adapter https://smile.amazon.com/gp/product/B00CPEZ4J6/ref oh aui detailpage o02 s00?ie UTF8&psc 1"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do they come inside a box? or are they just bubble wrapped?","answer":"They came with Amazon easy-open box, inside with bubble wrapped! Please believe the headset is more beautiful than his package!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatable with phones","answer":"Yes it is"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I'm trying to use this with the startech headset adapter on my xbox one. i can hear other people but they can't hear me. any idea why? thanks.","answer":"Hi friend, have you tried it on your PC, if you can use it on your PC, I think it must be the problem of your adapter. If not, please contact us, we wil do our best to help you solve this problem."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how long is cable ?","answer":"More than 7 ft!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use this for the xbox one","answer":"You couldn't unless you have an adapter!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the mic bendable","answer":"Yes, of course!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the warranty?","answer":"30 days money back and 365 days warranty!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do i hook it up to xbox one? I have adapter","answer":"It comes with three plugs. One is usb, the other two are different earplug connects. We are using it with WIIU."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is it compatible with cromebooks?","answer":"Yes, it is!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this headset be used with an Xbox 360?","answer":"I'm sorry not. But if you like this headset, you can bid a adapter together!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is trustworthy","answer":"I only use the headphone part not the mic, the headphones work great."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do you turn on the led lights?","answer":"You need to plug in the USB adapter, this adapter is the power supply of LED!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Which plug red or green works for Xbox one","answer":"Hello Rana, it can't if you don't have a adapter!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work with the new xbox one controllers with the 3.5mm plug?","answer":"Yes, it will!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work with the PS4?","answer":"Sorry but not!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with mac?","answer":"For 15in &17in. If yours is 13in, please search: B014H4MVY2!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there an adapter out there to make the mic and the headset into one plug? my laptop only has the headset port and has no mic port.","answer":"Yes, of course. You can search it on Amazon!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How does it work when I plug it in the computer the people can't hear me","answer":"Have you pluged the 3.5mm red connector!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatible for wii u?","answer":"If it have two ports that you need and then I believe it's okay"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this headset compatible with Iphone 5s and any other mobile devices?","answer":"Of course, but if you want to use the Mic function, you have to buy a 2 to 1 adapter!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work on ps3","answer":"Sorry but not!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it work for wii u.    Both of them","answer":"I'm not sure but I think it does if not there's adapters that you can get"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this fit a 9 year old child?","answer":"It's quite large for kids. But you can try this one! http://www.amazon.com/dp/B013S4CBOC!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will all functions work if only plugged in via USB?","answer":"No, USB is only for the LED lighting!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it have in game volume or only voice volume","answer":"Both"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use the mic and headphone without using the usb?","answer":"Yes, the USB is the power supply for LED. Not mic and headphone. So if you don't plug USB, you can't experience the LED function!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How many cords to plug in, and can you link them together so they dont tangle?","answer":"Hey friend, this design is very reasonable. There 3 plugs, but they never tangle, because they only separated only a little distance to the plugs. What's more, the cable is nylon material. Hard and not easy to tangle!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it a normal headphone jack or what","answer":"My daughter plugs into her computer just like normal headphones"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do they work for Ipads?","answer":"Only used to listen!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does the mic work with voice recognition?","answer":"This depends on your software, not our headset!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work on xbox one?","answer":"I'm sorry, but not!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use this on my dahon d7 folding bike?","answer":"As long as diameters match. I suppose so."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this fit a 30mm inside diameter headtube?","answer":"Size 1-1/8  34mm I.D. Headtube""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this for scooters or bike?","answer":"Scooter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this fit a lucky scooter deck with a lucky scooter ls fork?thanks","answer":"I think it only fits bike headsets"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with the star nut?","answer":"yes it does"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is this compatible with clarity professional xlc3.5hs?","answer":"As long as the phone has a 2.5 mm headphone jack input the comdio H403VP5 should work fine. i am using mine on a clarity professional XLC3.4 and i love it , especially because the hands free operation allows me to walk around my house and outside with my cordless phone. the volume and mute feature are also a plus, and the clarity of the tones and sounds are so awesome that i can talk and hear on the phone without my hearing aids."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work on PS3?","answer":"No, sorry ,it can't  .the G9000 headphone just work on PS4"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the cable length?","answer":"I measured mine and its about 7 feet."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for Xbox 360?","answer":"Sorry , it can't  .Just for PS4"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have a mic monitor or like a feedback like turtle beaches","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do you make the mic work it doesn't work for me?","answer":"Maybe your computer is a universal computer,the headphone and microphone  port are independent.But,this  Headset with one 3.5mm combo headphone/microphone connector, only suitable for PS4, mobile phones ,tablets, laptops(with 3.5mm combo headphone/microphone port). Advices: 1.You can use the mic when you plug it into mic hole OR you can use the headphone when you plug it into headphone hole.  2.You can choose the other one (G2000)in our store,the mic and headphone ports of g2000 are combined together. By the way,This headset is NOT USB-Headset, The USB interface is only used for power supply to LED light. No driver needed, Plug and play.   If you still have other questions, Don't hesitate to contact our support team simpeak.us@gmail.com"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the mic removable?","answer":"Yes ,But can't be separated"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If you have an adaptor does it work for xbox one","answer":"Yes it does. Enjoy"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can it play game sound?","answer":"To get the mic to work go to recording devices in the playback menu, enable the headphones input, and the adjust the gain structure."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for ps4?","answer":"Yes!! It works just like any other brand!! Excellent quality would recommend!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for xbox one?","answer":"Thanks for your inquiry, it just works with PS4. Hope this is helpful for you."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there seround sound","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for ps4","answer":"Hello, yes, it can use for PS4"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I have a thing to put the mic in, for ps4","answer":"No, just use the headshet"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a bottun to change the voice chat sound and in game sound?","answer":"There should be an option in game or on the computer"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does the mic turn off when u swivel it parallel to the headset piece?","answer":"n No it does not"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the mic Compatible with PC","answer":"Yes the mic is compatible my son has yet to try it but he says it comes with the plugs needed to connect it to the PC. Let me know if you have any other questions. We bought these for him to use on his Xbox One."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for computers","answer":"Yes unless you need a USB mic"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with my rca office phone rca2542d?  it has a 2.5mm headset jack.","answer":"Yes. This works with any phone which has a 2.5mm headset jack."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I answer and hang up on calls with this headset","answer":"No, answer & hang up are done by the phone."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have been through many headsets that stop working withing 6 mos to a year.  This product has a multi-year warranty.  What exactly does that mean?","answer":"Dear Thank an inquiry. The product has two years warranty. Within the warranty, a repair service may charge administrative fee $10 plus the shipping."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this be worn on the right ear?","answer":"Thank your inquiry. Yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with my mobile phone?","answer":"I don't think so as the jack is much smaller.  There may be an adapter but I don't know for sure."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this headset work with the base of the older plantronic T10 base?","answer":"Thank your inquiry. For the Plantronics T10 base, the following model will work. ASIN B0181V2R6Y   HeadsetsBank"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why are the first 3 pictures a different product from the last 4 pictures? What product are you actually selling ?","answer":"The first 3 pictures about the whole product.the last 4 about aparts,it's same product.just picture angle and visual effect is different"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how come mine wont work i cant talk.","answer":"check out your device drivers on your computer. Find the microphone driver on your computer and enable it. If you need driver like I did then order different headset that comes with the little cd to install the driver onto your computer. One that I have found that comes with this is sades 7.1"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can you listen to youtube videos on this?","answer":"Yeah"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is the cable?","answer":"RCA Audio convert cable length: Approx 1.6m XBOX 360 Convert cable length: Approx 1.0m"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it work for xbox one?","answer":"Sorry, it is not compatible with PS4 Xbox one. It could work with PCs, PS2, PS3, Xbox 360."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this item come with the Charging case?","answer":"Yes it did."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will it work with ATT&T z222?","answer":"Any phone and any network"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"WILL THIS WORK WITH A pANTECH p6020","answer":"Yes. If you buy it to link it to your phone just go to your bluetooth option and scan until its linked up with both phone and ear piece"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does It have caller id?, I mean, if I link my contact's number with  names,  does it announces  the name of the contact that is calling?","answer":"Yes it will tell you hoo is calling if thay are in your contacts."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this headset  always listening " or do you have to press a button to use voice commands?"","answer":"The BT is always listening, but you will still need to activate the microphone on your phone to talk."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What do you mean by 25% smaller body size compared to voyager hd pro? also, what's the other difference between this and the pro version?","answer":"The  HD Pro was replaced by this unit. This unit also has voice commands.  The charger on this unit was also change to a proprietary charging system which I do not particularly care for. The pro uses Micro USB charging which is much more convenient for me because I have several micro USB chargers. The new charger is magnetic and the magnetic hold is not very strong so when I charge it in my car it sometimes becomes disconnected and does not charge.  Other than the charger I am a fan of this newer model ."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can we listen music","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this device pair with and existing BT300 USB adapter?","answer":"Hi John,  Yes! The Voyager Legend is compatible with the BT300.   DealFisher Customer Care"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i have a bluetooth in my pc. can i use this hadset with skype?","answer":"I've used mine on Skype"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this bluetooth have solar recharge capabilities? I know this may be a silly question, this is something I read on Groupon.","answer":"No, this one does not.  But once charged it has, I believe, hours talk time.  I know 5 for sure but thinking 6.  It has 2 separate ways to charge.  An electric plug in, and a USB charger."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How i connect bluetooth","answer":"You put the device in pairing mode by holding the  call answer " button while powering on. Then put the phone in Bluetooth Settings and pairing mode usually that way.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this come with the wall charger and cord for $49.99?","answer":"Yes, but don't do it. But it new on here for around $85 all in. The refurb quality is crap. I just threat out now that the new one from Amazon just arrived."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this include the magnetic charger clip? (Also does it include the USB charger, car adapter, alternative sized earbud, plantronics voice recogni?)","answer":"Yes to the magnetic clip, it has the USB wall charger, not the car adapter, nor alternate earbuds (just one size) and the plantronics voice recognition feature is built in (Answer/Ignore, etc)."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do i return for warranty?","answer":"Go to https://www.plantronics.com and click on warranty or https://warranty.plantronics.com"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"it has warrantee or not ?","answer":"According to the description,  This Certified Refurbished product is factory refurbished, shows limited or no wear, and includes all original accessories plus a 90-day warrant ". So yes.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I pair 3 Phones in this item? I only use one phone at the time.","answer":"I would thing you could pair this headset to 3 phones, since you use them singly.  That way it only pick up the phone that on at the time.  If all three are on, that could be problematic."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it adaptable to be used in either ear?","answer":"yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"hello dear friend this item Have the original packaging?","answer":"No it was wrapped in plastic in a box with a charger but not in original Voyager packaging"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this come with everything I need to use on a VOIP phone?  Will I need to buy some sort of wireless adapter?","answer":"It will only come with the headset and wall plug and magnetic charger. If you need a Bluetooth USB for a pc, you will need that separate."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use a universal usb bluetooth adapter to pair it with a PC?","answer":"Not that i know of.   I believe it has to be the plantronics usb adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the talk time?","answer":"Seven hours  Is the best in the market I purchase one for myself and in two month I purchase 5 more for family and friend of the trucking business"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work macbook?","answer":"Mine never worked since I got it. Cannot get in touch with on time warranty(that name us a joke) have been trying to talk to them for 2 weeks - leave messages they never call back. Will not buy any electronis off amazon unless I can find out who backs the warranty"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have an older samsung flip phone, will it work with it?","answer":"Yes if it supports the type of bluetooth."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it connect to multiple devices","answer":"yes and it plays extremely well with others, one tap on the main button and it switches to wherever it should be.  I really don't think that you can go wrong with this thing aside from it only having the proprietary charger it is the best thing since sliced bread.  Do yourself a favor and get the charging case for it as well then you will have nothing to complain about.  LOL."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this Unit compatible with my Panasonic Cordless phone?","answer":"I would imagine if the phone is Bluetooth"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"difference between plantronics bluetooth 87300-41 and 87300-41-RB","answer":"Hey Arul, there is no difference. The RB is just for Refurbished. It's easier to identify the product. Hope this helps."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this reversable? - meaning you can swivel it for use on either ear?","answer":"Yes,Reversible.We can use in right or left ears."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it stay in place on your ear?","answer":"Yes but after a month of use people can no longer hear me for the distortion. I tried contacting the company but cannot get a response.  I would definitely stay away from pavilion electronics."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with a lumina 920 windows phone","answer":"Sorry, I do not know the answer to that question. However I have a iPhone 6 Plus if that helps you any"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do you redeem 90 day warranty?","answer":"Go to the Plantronics website. They are very good."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What's the difference with other same products?","answer":"So far this brand is so much better then any other. My number 1 choice"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do I need a computer to recharge?","answer":"No, mine came with its own charger. My only problem turned out to be, I use my blue tooth alot, alot, alot. I guess I wore it out. It wont charge anymore. I reviewed on you tube how to change the battery. They show a guy using a utility knife to access the battery. What the ...."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the distance you can talk away from your phone","answer":"Not very far."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hello, does this Plantronic lengend voyager bluetooth headset comes with a charger?","answer":"Hi Bob,  Yes! It comes with the USB charger.  Dealfisher Customer Care"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Que accesorios trae?","answer":"Trae su cargador,gomitas de respuesto para el auricular,y el manual"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long before the battery life starts to degrade?","answer":"I believe I got a bad device I purchased 2 earpieces and mine does not work, however the other is just fine. He charges it once every 3-4days.... And I talk to him all the time."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the Iphone 6 plus? I need to have a bluetooth that I can speak commands such as answer, ignore ect.","answer":"Yes it does . I have a iPhone 5 also steams music."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this Bluetooth pick up a lot of background noise?  Very annoying . . . .","answer":"Yes, it is noise canceling and does it quite well I may add."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Cuantas horas aguanta de carga","answer":"The question is in Spanish I don't read or speak Spanish"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is it compatible to iphone 11?","answer":"Hello! Yes, the M70 headset is compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth headsets and audio streaming. Most smartphones nowadays are Bluetooth enabled so it should work. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance or have further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long before the battery life starts to degrade?","answer":"Ive had mine about 6 months and seems to hold a charge as well as it did the day I got it. Only thing I don't like about it is the ear piece. The old model fit better. This sometimes comes off my ear. But all in all a good blue tooth for the money."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this have a charger","answer":"Yes it does"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what is the talk time on the M70?","answer":"Hello! The M70 has up to 11 hours of Talk time."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"After pairing, will it connect automatically if it is turned off and then turned on again?","answer":"Ye"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this ompatible with the iPhone 8/ 8 plus?","answer":"Yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Bought it in Nov 2015. The button that controls sound has fallen off, shouldn't this be covered under the warranty since it is less than a year old?","answer":"I advise you to contact the manufacturer in regards to any warranty questions or issues."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this device have called ID: announcing the caller's name from the cellular phone's contacts list, instead of just the caller's number? Thanx!","answer":"Mine does not.  But I do not have a smart phone.  It simply says,  Incoming call. """}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the ear piece comfortable in the ear?  Even for many hours ?","answer":"Yes, I wear this ear piece ever day and it is the most comfortable and best functioning blue tooth ear piece I have ever owned.  It also will effectively connect to two different sources.  Highly recommend."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Cuantas horas dura de carga ?","answer":"Hola! Nuestro M70 cuenta con alrededor de 11 horas de tiempo de conversaci n. El rendimiento depende de la bater a y puede variar en funci n del dispositivo. El tiempo de carga total es de dos horas. Si tienes alguna otra duda, no dudes en contactar a nuestro equipo al: 800-985-9815"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"we can use 220v ?","answer":"The charger is rated to 100 to 240V~ 50-60hrz.  Does this adequately address the issue?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I'm having a problem with plantronics m70, the call button doesn't work when i push it and try to answer the call, anyone else had this issue ?","answer":"Mine works fine. Does it work at all with your device? If not I would try and re-pair it again.."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can one buy replacement ear hooks?","answer":"Yes! ACthally the  ear hooks " & rubber ear piece are the same for the Voyager Edge.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatable with Apple watch","answer":"I'm not sure I use android"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I washed my plantronics m70 how do I fix it","answer":"You can try putting the Bluetooth headset in rice for a day then try charging it!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is this compatible with the Samsung note 2?","answer":"Hello, Yes, I'm currently using it on the Note 2, thank you."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the galaxy s7 edge?","answer":"Yes, you can even listen to your music   ~  very good product 4 the price.    575xp  hope it will help you."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"After charge, light is blue, red, then no light. record repeats  power on, power off - is this defective? will not pair with my kindle fire.","answer":"This sounds defective.  I  have used this model of blue tooth for years and not had that happen unless I took it too far from what it was connected."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is m70 compatible with the kindle fire 8 hd","answer":"Hello! Yes. The M70 headset is compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth headsets and audio streaming. Most smartphones and tablets nowadays are Bluetooth enabled so it should work. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance or have further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it read texts","answer":"Yes. I use it with a Samsung Galaxy Note4. You can also dictate texts. I replaced a $135 Bose with this and am very happy that I did."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with a tv bluetooth?","answer":"Hello! If your TV has a built-in Bluetooth chip that has the required profiles (HSP, HFP, A2DP) and a menu to select devices, the headset should work with it. We recommend you to test it and check your seller's return policy, in case it is not a fit for you!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"When the shipping come","answer":"This is not a question."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatible with iwatch?","answer":"I don't have a iwatch"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this tell you how charge is left","answer":"If the unit is off and you turn it on, hold it to your ear and the voice will tell how many hours it will work. 11 hours is a full charge."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it read and send text messages for you","answer":"Hello, Yes, I think so, Happy new Year."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How to return","answer":"Again I'm not sure"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work well for someone with large ears?","answer":"It should work fine I've used this very product for years with no issues"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will it work with a samsung SCH1400 cell phone","answer":"It will if it is a smart phone"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the M70 play the actual ringtone I have set in my phone or does it only play a chime to let me know that there's a call coming in?","answer":"Great question.  I actually don't know.  I didn't use it much and don't remember ever getting a call.  I would assume it will play whatever ringtone you have for a new incoming call, but the manual does say that when on a call, you get a ringtone.  Hope this helps.  Enjoy the day!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you ask for Siri with this device?","answer":"I think so. Mine stopped working before I got that involved in using it, but I'm pretty sure it would.."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have an ear bud","answer":"If I understand your question correctly! It goes in your ear, wouldn't that make it an air bud?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this go to Samsung s5","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"So you can connect two phones at one time","answer":"I was able to connect to devices at the same time and it will say  phone 1 " or  "phone 2 " connected.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the difference between the M70 and the M165?","answer":"Hello! thank you for reaching out. The main difference between the two models is the talk time, the M70 can give you up to 11 hours of talk time and the M165 up to 7 hours, other than that, both models are very similar in wearing style. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance or have further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work well for someone with small ears?","answer":"I believe so, because you can put the ear part in the ear you don't have to use the loop over the ear, it stays in with out which is how I wear it.  It is very good,"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this Bluetooth compatible with the Samsung Galaxy 7?","answer":"Good day to you... It will connect with any device.. Thanks."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is it compatible with samsung galaxy s9","answer":"I don't know. My phone is Samsung S7."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hi, did it comes diferent sizes of eartips in the box like S, M, L??","answer":"No. One-size."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How many mics does it have? The Edge call quality doesn't convince me. Is it a power switch or button for on/off? interchangeable earbuds?","answer":"It has just one mic. It has a power on / off switch. You can buy interchangeable earbuds!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are you able to connect 2 phones?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this headset read out the phone number of an incoming call?","answer":"NO IT JUST SAYS IN COMING CALL"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this connect to a lg stylo 4?","answer":"It will connect to any device which support Bluetooth, which most modern smart phones do."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the sound clear and loud?","answer":"Yes very clear"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Anybody have used it on windows 7? The mic doesn't work for me","answer":"I use this with my phone do can't answer if it works with your computer. Sorru"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use your voice to answer calls?","answer":"Hello, the M70 headset doesn't feature the ability to answer calls with your voice, for this purpose we recommend the Marque 2 M165 or our Voyager Series. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it come with and extra rubber piece that goes in your ear?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do I pair this with GooglexL2 ?","answer":"I do not know. Check with their website. I LOVE this headset!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it last more than 30 days ? I've had three different brand sets and they all died within 30 days or so. And I'm not a heavy user. Thanks.","answer":"Yes, it was a gift for my son and he loves it. Very reliable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with nokia lumina 635? older cell. bluetooth compatable. it is a windows phone... not i phone or android.","answer":"I'm not sure. The headset is Bluetooth v3.0 compatible."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this earpiece alert when I receive a text?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I Locate earpiece","answer":"I purchased this on amazon just this spring, retailers keep updating in stores but I like this model and found it here"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with a Blackberry phone?","answer":"You need a 2.5 adapter with it. ,"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I connect this to a cordless phone so I can take calls","answer":"It does not work for most cordless phones. You can buy an adapter though."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this headset be used on a landline telephone?","answer":"Yes, but it needs an adapter jack. I use it for both phones and is probably the best I've had for sound quality."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I use this with my work laptop and i am really loud to others on the conference line. any idea how i can turn the mic down?","answer":"If you have a windows laptop, you can go to the bottom right of your task bar, right click on the sound icon - playback devices - recording - right click on microphone, click on properties - levels, adjust accordingly, use a friend!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does music sound decent?","answer":"Yes - it sounds decent. But, my guess is that high end audio is not the target application for this product.  I use the headset for phone conversations (iPhone 6) during extended meetings and web conferences, and for that application it is the best I have found. Certainly better than any ear buds that I have seen or tried.  It does not have noise cancelling - a feature that you would really want when listening to music."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what kind of adapter jack?","answer":"If you are just using it for your I pad or phone, it uses a 3.5mm jack. If you want to use both the mic and earphones on the computer, use a splitter: 3.5mm to mic and headphone. This headset does not work with Steam."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this trrs or separate mic and headphone connectors?","answer":"It's a single pin connector for headphones and microphone.  I have used it with my cell phone (Samsung) and it works perfectly.  Also works on my computer."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the mic removable? And what size is the mic jack?","answer":"No. Why would you want to remove it? The arm is adjustable, if you want to swing it up or down. The mic jack is standard. It fits in cell phones and computers."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this  be used with dragon?","answer":"Yes, as long as your computer recognizes the device it should work with any application."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I've been searching to purchase replacement ear covers.   Is that possible?","answer":"There are many sites that sell replacement ear covers.  Be sure to measure the opening and the total size of the earpiece in question.  The cover needs to have sufficient overlap to keep it from slipping off.  I've bought replacements for my headsets when they wear out.  Also, watch out for where the cord and mounts connect to the speaker."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work on my android tablet?","answer":"Yes, it should.  I have an android smart phone, and this headset works great with it."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Replacement foam ear pads - has anyone been able to find any replacement ear pads that will work with this headset?","answer":"No, the headset usually dies before I would need to replace the foam ear pads. Although I love this headset.  I keep buying it, as it's the most comfortable headset there is, and I do a lot of voicing online.  I even use it for singing at online open mics. I did find windscreen foam covers give it an even better quality sound. I didn't help, but You deserved an answer, hope you find your ear pads!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Would this headset work with a asus chromebook flip c100pa for doing voice calls?","answer":"I'm not sure, I don't know that computer, but if you have just one jack on the laptop, then you need a Y splitter.  Like this: https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00PYZ2BT4/ref ppx yo dt b asin title o04 s00?ie UTF8&psc 1"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Would this work on my Pixel smart phone.  I don't know the size of the plug on my smart phone","answer":"This headset worked for about an hour then nothing."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is the cord?","answer":"The cord is approx. 70 inches long."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with gaming? like can i chat with it? and will it work?","answer":"Yes a headset is a combination headphone and microphone.  So you can use it for chatting on any platform that allows voice.  You may have to get a Y splitter if you don't have a machine with analog (2) jacks."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I didn't see any battery requirements. How does the noise cancelling works? If any.","answer":"This headset does not require batteries. The headset has a 3.5 mm jack on it. All you have to do is plug it into your computer. On the headset, there are On-cord controls make it easy to quickly adjust your headset volume and mute the microphone."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with the xbox one?","answer":"Yeah of course , but you must have an adapter to use this beautiful headset"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Would the microphone and speakers work on a computer that only has one 3.5mm port that is shared for speakers and microphone?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does sound come from both ears?","answer":"yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you be in Skype and listen to music with this headset?","answer":"I'm unsure ...I can be in Second Life on voice and still hear music. I think it depends on the platform.  It's a headset, so I imagine anything you can hear without a headset on you can hear with one.  Try listening on your speakers can you play music and hear another person on Skype at the same time?"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how long is the wire?","answer":"Looks to be 5 or 6 feet, I didn't uncoil."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have a dell inspiron n5110 laptop and i can't get the headphones to work in either port. do i need a splitter adaptor? works fine on my phone.","answer":"These headphones have both sound output and mic in one connector.  If the laptop has separate jacks for each, then yes you'd need the right kind of splitter type thing."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this work on an ipad air","answer":"Yes.  All new smartphones and tablets have mic capable headphone ports."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Anyone know if this will also work with a portable DVD player?","answer":"As long as it has an auxiliary port, yes it'll definitely work!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it be used for gaming","answer":"I use it for web conferences, can speak and hear and others can hear me.  It fits the 3.5 mm jack, ,and some people think it is harder to hear me when I use it than when I use my Logitech USB headset.    Hope this helps!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Anyone know what the single jack connects into?  I'm just looking for an old school mic. that connects to a pink analog 3.5mm jack","answer":"That will work just fine, works with laptops, tvs, phones, anything with a 3.5mm jack. You can also use a splitter for the mic/headphones if there is an input for the separate functions"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this fit comfortably, or is it pretty tight?","answer":"It is adjustable, and I find it very comfortable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use it for gaming","answer":"Depends what you're gaming with. PC gaming you will need a splitter to hook this up to a soundcard. It's a 4-pin 3.5mm plug, meaning it has both L+R Audio, and Mic in 1. I can't remember if it came with one or not.."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What can I do to ensure my M70 ear piece continues to work properly after dropping it into a cup of coffee","answer":"Hello, unfortunately, the M70 doesn't have sweat or moisture protection. We recommend you to let it air dry and test. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Would this work with an itouch?  i have tried headsets of this type, and they appear to pair but i don't get any sound through bluetooth.","answer":"It works with my I phone 5. I do not know about the touch."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compartible with I phones 8s and 10","answer":"I don't have a iPhone I have note 8"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this play media sound also ir just phone calls","answer":"It does play media"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is the manufacturers warranty","answer":"user guide doesn't say, only gives webpage www.plantronics.com/documentation"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What's the difference between the M70 and M90?","answer":"Bluntly, the M90, to this point in my usage of it, doesn't SUCK!  Tried 2 of the M70s BOTH were horrible!!!  So far M90 so good"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What size earpiece does it come with ?? Thank you","answer":"Mine came with a medium."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work sony xperia xa ultra","answer":"Yes it worked fine for a while.  I got it as a gift for my son, but after several months, it quit working and he said there was nothing he could do to fix it.  Not sure what went wrong."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I cannot get it paired to my I-phone any suggestions?","answer":"Love it. It’s perfect. I can   Listen to music while I work"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have an M55. I wear it at least 14 hours every day. Very comfortable in my ear, I don't even realize it is there. Will the M70 be as comfortable?","answer":"I do not use the earloop, I only use the tips.  I wear it all day and I usually forget I'm wearing it.  This is the best deal I've ever had on a bluetooth.  Inexpensive, incredibly comfortable, 11-hour battery life.  I bought a second so I could charge one while using the other on really long days."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will this unit connect to a windows based windows 10 computer?","answer":"Hello! The M70 is compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth headsets. However, as you may know, your computer is equipped with an internal Bluetooth adapter. Bluetooth technology works through several Bluetooth profiles, and these are the ones that the Bluetooth card should have to at least allow a connection to the headphones: Audio transmissions, Hands Free (HFP) and/or Headset (HSP) Bluetooth profiles. Nowadays many computers have Bluetooth built-in but not all of them support Bluetooth headsets. Many times, these drivers are not installed by default - even on new computer installations. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you require further assistance!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How does the headset charge with the provided cable adapter?","answer":"You have to plug the small end of the cable in the back of the head set closest to where you power it on at."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the ear pice on this model (plt m70) small, medium, large?","answer":"Hello! The M70 comes with a Medium size ear tip. Here are the part numbers in case you need them: Large: 201955-03, Medium: 201955-02, Small: 201955-01."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this earpiece multipoint?","answer":"Yes it is multipoint."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this earpiece supposed to come with additional earpieces (in several sizes). I've never had one that didn't.   Thanks for  info!!!","answer":"Nope nothing else"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If not already wearing this, how easy is it to start using it mid call?","answer":"If the device your talking on is already paired with the M70, it's no problem. Just put the M70 Bluetooth in your ear and turn it on. It will take a few seconds to connect to the device your using. Simple!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatible with galaxy s8","answer":"Hi! Yes, the M70 is compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth headsets. Most Smartphones nowadays have BT built-in and support BT Headsets. If you have further questions, feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this last 11 hrs just like plantronics 55m?","answer":"yes, yes and i love my plantronics. second one i brought, because i lose the first one."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you have connected this bluetooth headset to your laptops thru bluetooth?","answer":"I connected to my tablet, I'm sure if the laptop has Bluetooth capabilities you can connect."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why does it drop calls?  The phone is right next to me when it happens.","answer":"Cuz it sucks does the same time and it does a noise when a friend uses the same one cheap I got ripped off"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is the talk time after being charged","answer":"Hi! The M70 has up to 11 hours of talk time. Please note performance is dependent upon battery and may vary by device. Feel free to contact our Customer Care at: 800-985-9815 if you have other questions!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with the Kindle products?","answer":"It paired easily with my Kindle Fire HD."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it announce the caller?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with samsung galaxy j7 sky pro","answer":"yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does a read text messages","answer":"Hello, I do not think so, Happy new Year."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it read who's calling?","answer":"no it does not.  it just rings.  it does not says anything except how much pwr is left. Id of the caller is not cue thru the M70.  You can get that info from your smart phone, but then this defies the use of a handless unit."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Goodnight! Is it compatible with Samsung S5? and can it be used in the left ear?","answer":"Don't know if it is compatible with Samsung S5 or not.  I always use mine on the right ear.  Have not tried to use on left ear."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What size is this?    the description below states 4 x 1.7 x 7.1 inches but that cannot be correct....... tia","answer":"It's about one and three quarters of an inch long, and about five eights of an inch wide."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the LG G5 ?","answer":"Yes, I have the g3, the g5 will be able to use any Bluetooth device"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this be paired with two phones simultaneously.","answer":"It would have to be paired one at a time"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work for the LG V10","answer":"Hello, As long as the LG V10 supports Bluetooth devices, thank you."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a physical on/off switch that moves (from on to off and off to on), or just a power button to hold down for a few seconds?","answer":"Just a power button to hold down for a couple of seconds."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with a charger?","answer":"Yes, it does."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"El producto m70 viene en caja original ???","answer":"Si"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this headset work with my lg442 flip phone?  the flip phone is bluetooth capable.","answer":"Neither the headset or the phone manual say it doesn't. My advice is to buy one and if the setup fails to connect then return the same day."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it stay powered on while charging?","answer":"11 huurs"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the iPhone 4?","answer":"I'm not sure about the 4, but I use it with my iPhone 5s.  I would assume it would work with all iPhones since it works with my current phone.  It is the best ear piece I have used to date.  Great wait and talk time.  I can leave it in my bag for 2-3 weeks not used and then it has 11 hours of talk time when I fire it up.  Great piece."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this unit come with a recharging unit or cord?","answer":"Yes is comes with a usb to plug in unit."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are they compatible with the Galaxy Note 9?","answer":"I connect modern PC and Laptop, it’s impossible that it’s not connect with this. Please, only verify BT version of the celular and compare."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I watch movies and listen with m70","answer":"yes, via bluetooth"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work with a Windows PC?","answer":"I don't know , I went through a couple people at Amazon and ordering the wrong thing until someone said for my kindle and apple products I needed the ADP2 (radio wave?)   I found as long as what I was ordering had this it worked.  Some phones will take this and some won't .  Check with who you bought your computer with or harass Amazon until you find someone who understands what the ADP2 works with.   Plantronic's are great products, watch for listening time also some are 11 hours and some are 7 hours.  And they only take 20 minutes to recharge."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"My bluetooth is paired to 2 phones. i want to unpair it from one phone but can't. is there a way to reset the bluetooth completely?","answer":"Hello  Thanks for reaching out.  The headset is a slave device, all changes in connection has to be done on phone level. You need to forget the device on the Bluetooth list of the phone to remove it.  Kind regards"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is itcompatiable with LG V30?","answer":"Hi! Yes, the M70 headset is compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth headsets and audio streaming. Most smartphones nowadays are Bluetooth enabled so it should work. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance or have further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it be worn on either ear?","answer":"Yes just turn plastic hook arond"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the playtronics m70 a multipoint with the same features as the playtronics e 50?","answer":"Hello! No, they have a few differences. The M70 is a newer version, hence it has HD voice and has the following Bluetooth profiles: A2DP, AVRCP, HFP, HSP (The explorer 50 does not have AVRCP). It is important to mention as well that the explorer 50 has already been discontinued. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you have other questions!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this bluetooth come with the hook that goes around your ear?","answer":"No but it is comfortable"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this have a mute button?","answer":"Not that I know of but you can always use the mute button on your phone"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is the headset compatible with the blackberry Q10?","answer":"i believe so"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the iPhone 5C?","answer":"Yes it is"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What generation cvc noise technology does this have?","answer":"N/A"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If you are listening to a podcast, is it possible to pause playback using the bluetooth's controls without touching the phone?","answer":"N/A"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do you rate the m70 for an android device?.","answer":"10"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with a charger","answer":"yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Compatible for smartphones 4 & 5","answer":"I have the Samsung Galaxy 4 and it works.  I really love this Bluetooth!  I've had other brands but this one is the best by far!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there a wall charger in the package, or just a usb cable? This has been asked, but answered both ways","answer":"Just a USB cable"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work for video conferencing on a Chromebook?","answer":"Hello! No. This headset is intended to work and connect to mobiles and tablets.  If you are looking for a headset to work with your PC for video conferencing we recommend you to take a look at our UC versions or wired headsets. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have hands-free answer and ignore?","answer":"Yes this device is great!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I was only needing one Bluetooth not to so if you could please send one back","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"looking for all  sold by amazom over the ear phone bluetooth","answer":"Sure"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"this headset pairs with my macbook air, but it will not reconnect after it wakes from sleep mode. can anyone make a suggestion?","answer":"Hello! Once the device the headset is connected to, is powered off and on, it is that device that should request a connection. If it is not connecting, please try powering off the headset and turning back on (once the PC is awake). If you continue to experience difficulties, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatible with the iwatch 4 series 40?","answer":"Don’t know- don’t have an I watch"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long does it take to charge ?","answer":"One hour or at most 2 hours"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Manufacturing  phone number","answer":"Unknown at this time"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can two of these be paired and used with an iphone xs max and hear stereo?","answer":"Hi! The M70 does provide media audio and has multipoint feature as well which enables you to pair and connect your headset to two different Bluetooth audio devices at once.  Note that you will not be able to use two devices simultaneously  instead, the benefit is that you will be able to answer an incoming phone call from either device using the headset. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you require further assistance!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What kind of distance range can you take this M70 from your phone. A lot of the Motorola's boast 300 ft. I wondered what you got are getting with this","answer":"I've managed about 100ft obstructed from my phone.  I've not tried to see how far I can go unobstructed.  I know you can go farther unobstructed."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"The small silicone ear bud insert, became loose and fell off multiple times, should I ask for refund or will support cover this?","answer":"I JUST ADORE THE BLUE TOOTH,  BECAUSE IF IT FUNCTIONALITY,   IT FITS PROPERLY AN HAS NEVER FELL OFF.  I HAVE ORDERD (3) AN HOPE THAT THIS PRODUCT STAYS ON THE MARKET.  I SLEEP WITH IT IN MY EAR ALMOST NITELY !    WHICH PART ARE YOU REFERRING TOO THAT KEEPS COMING OFF ??  TRY TO FOLLOW THE DIRECTIONS MORE CLOSELY.  I RATE THIS A (10) TEN."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What's the range on this Bluetooth?","answer":"About 30 feet"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I don't see an indicator or a  charge " light, does this have one?"","answer":"Yes. Its on the outside. Red when charging. Blue when in use"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you answer incoming calls by saying  Answer " like on the M55 model?"","answer":"Not sure I press the button on the unit"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If it in fact doesn't come with a charger, what type/kind of connection does it have that I will need to provide?","answer":"Just something that accepts a usb plug. Make sure you get the ear loop. Mine came without it."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i listen to siriusxm radio in my car  through this headset? The car has siriusxm and bluetooth installed.","answer":"I have been able to successfully connect to many other Bluetooth devices with the M70 like laptops, tablets and phones, but I am not sure about cars.   The Plantronics site has specs for the M70 showing Bluetooth v3.0. It should pair with any BT 3 or 2 device. That said, most Bluetooth-enabled cars will pair with phones and Bluetooth media players. Paring a car's Bluetooth with a headset may not be an option. I was only able to pair phones and media players with my last car."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this bluetooth headset compatible with mi redmi3s mobile?","answer":"If it has bluetooth then yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the plantronics m70 compatible with the standard moto g6?","answer":"I have never used moto g6"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the voltage","answer":"Hi! The M70 can be charged with a AC adapter that does not exceed 5 volts. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you have other questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How many hours of phone-calling? I don't see anyting on product description...","answer":"A LONG time!  This is the best one I've had yet.  I would estimate about 10 hours."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatable with the gallexy s3","answer":"My blue tooth was compatible with my Galaxy 4.  Hope this helps!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with iphone11pro max?","answer":"I have no idea. It works with my samsung galaxy, and it works great."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Este articulo es nuevo,sin uso?","answer":"The one I bought was new.   El que compr  era nuevo."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If it doesnt come with a charger, how do you charge it?","answer":"it does come with a charger"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compataible with Samsung 7s","answer":"Yes it is! I checked my mobile carriers website where I got it from, and they listed almost all galaxy devices including samsung galaxy s7 and s7edge.  Hope it helps, and if so, please purchase from me. Thank you"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have volume control?","answer":"Yes but it doesn't get very loud."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how loud is the  volume","answer":"The volume is excellent"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can you listen to music with this bluetooth?","answer":"Yes you can"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this pair with a galaxy A20","answer":"Hello, if the A20 has bluetooth capabilities,  should work fine."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with a kindle fire hd 8?","answer":"Hi!  I believe so.  I use it with Samsung devices and it works well. So it should work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the Iphone 6?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatable with the Galaxy's s9?","answer":"Not sure.  I have never had any Galaxy s9."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the plantronics m70 compatible with iphone 8 and iphone xr ?","answer":"Hello, the M70 headset is designed to work with devices that have Bluetooth, and the required profiles (HFP, HSP, A2DP). In this case, it will work correctly with iPhones. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I access my google assistant from the headset?","answer":"Hello! Yes. You will need to press and hold the call button for 2 seconds for your phone assistant to come up. Please feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the plantronics m70 compatable with Nokia 520 ?","answer":"I already responded to this question and then did some research.  http://ca.windowscentral.com/nokia-lumia-520-bluetooth-headsets.htm?sort by selection name   go to this web page I would say the answer is yes and the talk time is 11 hours for this model.  I love it."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the plantronics m70 compatible with iphone 8 and iphone xr ?","answer":"Hello, the M70 headset is designed to work with devices that have Bluetooth, and the required profiles (HFP, HSP, A2DP). In this case, it will work correctly with iPhones. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Anyone have connection issues? m70 will disconnect from iphone 11. i will have to manually reconnect. i didn’t have this issue with my iphone x.","answer":"My first one would randomly disconnect then immediately reconnect after I had it awhile. Never did it while I was using it though. Seemed to disconnect when I had other items paired to it also (but not connected) but it always reconnected as soon as it was finished saying  bluetooth disconnected ". The other 4 I've owned never did, including the current one. It only disconnects when I get too far from the phone as usual.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work with galaxy s7?","answer":"Yes, I've used this with the Galaxy S7 and j7. Hands-free dialing from the phone book also works very well."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does earhook swivel?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how do you charge the M70 Bluetooth headset?","answer":"There is an included ~12” USB to micro-USB cable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the range from the Bluetooth?","answer":"If the phone is in the house I can go about 25' outside before it loses connection.  If both are outside with nothing blocking them it'll stay locked on probably about 10' further."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it stay in your ear without the hook?","answer":"Yes but how well likely depends on your individual ear structure. Mine stays in really well using only the ear gel (soft ear loop that goes inside the ear) and I feel confident it is staying put. Very comfy!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the M70 work with Android phones?","answer":"Hello, Yes, I think so, thank you."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what version of bluetooth does it use?","answer":"I believe it is V.1.3, I have a 1 1/2 year sold Galaxy s6 and it works well with that, no problems"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the quality of the microphone? Are other people able to hear ok or do you need to speak loudly for them to hear you?","answer":"Hello! All of our headsets have noise-cancelling microphones. This is a pretty good one for an entry level. If you're looking for something with a stronger noise cancelling microphone, then you might want to take a look at our Voyager Legend or the Voyager 5200. If you have any further questions, please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"voice command?","answer":"No it doesn't"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it announce the caller?","answer":"yes it do announce the caller."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the m70 comes with a charger?","answer":"It comes with a cord to connect to either a wall charger or portable one, but it doesn’t come with a defined charger."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it have good range","answer":"Bluetooth has 11 hours of talk time very clear sound and does have very good range very good Bluetooth to have."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this specific headset completely black, or is it one with either red, white or blue stripe on top and bottom of the headset","answer":"I've bought 3 and all have a white stripe around the perimeter."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does is function as a normal microphone for podcasts etc?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I just received the headset yesterday and the sound has alot of static.  Does anyone else have this issue?","answer":"Have you tested your phone with a different device? Because I dont have this issue. My unit works fine no static at all. Could be a faulty device, or your connection is weak. However a weak connection would usually show itself as an intermittent lose in audio not static though."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this be paried with a laptop for conference calls?","answer":"Hello! Our M70 is compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth headsets  However, please note that Bluetooth technology works through different profiles. As you know, your computer is equipped with an internal Bluetooth adapter. These are the ones that the Bluetooth card should have to at least allow a connection to the headphones: Audio transmissions, Hands Free (HFP) and/or Headset (HSP) Bluetooth profiles. Nowadays many computers have Bluetooth built-in but not all of them support Bluetooth headsets. Many times, these drivers are not installed by default   even on new computer installations. We recommend you to check out our UC line of products which are designed for mobile and PC connectivity. If you have any further questions, feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this bluetooth headset compatible to any laptops with bluetooth?","answer":"I'm not sure if every laptop would be compatible. It uses v3.0 Bluetooth and I have paired it to my MacBook Air before."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is it compatible w/panasonic cordless phone system?","answer":"I’m unsure but it is Bluetooth."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it cancel outside noise for the person calling you","answer":"Yes outside noise to a degree but not close up noise such as running water, paper bags, ect... for the price is a damn good unit you will not go wrong"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If you're side by side with someone, who also is using a M70, and on a conference call, will you get a bad echo?","answer":"Have not tried but would think so"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it announce who the caller is?","answer":"no"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Whats the time frame for music","answer":"When brand new, after a full charge I would see 12 to 14 hours of talk time.   I have one iPad Pro,  four iPads, and two iphones.    All things considered, the Plantronics works all day long.  Only on few occasions, have I ran out of power. (The plantronics will hibernate if not used  Over a period of time).  if you are not listening to music all day, and talking on the,  or a lot of dictation, it will be a great choice.    Be sure to initially do a full charge!   ONLY RECHARGE  when you need to (when the battery is empty or near empty).    IT WILL WORK GREAT AND LAST A LONG TIME!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can it connect to 2 devices !","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How long is talk time when fully charged?","answer":"I believe it’s 11 hours"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"what is the diameter of the piece that goes into the ear? I have a Jabra and it is about 9/16 .  Thats too big for my ear."","answer":"I measured this it’s 9/16 too. But the part that hooks over your ear is very tight i tried to stretch mine in hot water but it went right back. It’s so tight it hurts my ear after wearing it awhile sound is great though"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how many hours does this  bluetooth charge?","answer":"Full charge in 2 hrs or less.  Up to 11 hrs talk time, up to 16 days standby time, up to 180 days DeepSleep standby mode."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can m70 platonics work on s7 active","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"are they compatible to sumsung j7 prime?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this Bluetooth have the capability to check text messages with the touch of the button, will it play my voicemails, can I send text messages?","answer":"Yes to both..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does anyone no how to change the language from spanish to english.","answer":"Hold button down listen to instructions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how do it charge","answer":"Charge it through a micro usb cable.  However, I DO NOT RECOMMEND THIS PRODUCT!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How well does it cancel out background noise?","answer":"I wear it to bed to watch Netflix etc. so there really isn't any background noise to speak of.  I have been really impressed overall and plan to buy another one for my husband. Sorry I don't have an answer but thanks for letting me say positive things about this product"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"compatible  with google xl2?","answer":"Hi! Yes, the M70 headset is compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth headsets and audio streaming. Most smartphones nowadays are Bluetooth enabled so it should work. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance or have further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the LG leon lgt?","answer":"I do not know but I am sure it will it is very simple to pair I have a Samsung S7 Edge"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it pair with google pixel XL","answer":"It pairs via Bluetooth and works well with my phone"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can other person hear you?","answer":"If you are asking if person on a phone call can hear you, then absolutely yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"m70 or m90?","answer":"I have not tried M90 but M70 is great."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can these plug into the audio of an airplane?","answer":"Yes ...It control your Music and steaming audio using headset buttons"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it have a pause/play switch or button?","answer":"Yes press both up & down volume buttons at the same time to pause/play."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the diametere of the piece that goes into the ear?","answer":"Hello! The M70 ear tip is 14.5 mm long. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this come with power supply?","answer":"Hi! No, the M70 includes a standard micro-USB cable and in order to charge it you can use any 5 volt charger or USB port. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you have other questions!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the galaxy s7 edge?","answer":"I'm not sure. I assume that most phones if not all would be compatible.  I have a Sony phone.  This is the best Bluetooth I've had yet. If I were you, I'd call your phone carrier and ask their tech support."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is this compatible with Samsung galaxy s3?","answer":"Yes, I use the headset with my Galaxy S3."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it compatible with zte android phones?","answer":"I would assume so. I am an apple gal but I don't know why it wouldn't. Great comfortable earpiece!"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What is the return policy on this product?","answer":"i know of the amazon return policy but I lost my last one long after the warranty was up"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is caller I'd option available","answer":"This product is a blue tooth headset that is wireless and does not have that functionality. The only product that I know that would come close is Plantronic's Legend working in conjunction with your cell phone contact list it allows you to accept or reject calls. i use the Jabra GO 6400 with my landline and my phones do not store that information nor does this particular model have that capability."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this compatible with the Jabra Go 6470 base station?","answer":"Yes this works with the 6470 base"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this headset for ps4 and xbox 360? or is that only the a40 gen 2 model that can be used for both platforms?","answer":"As long as your controller has a normal headphone jack it should work on Xbox One or PS4 I'm not sure about Xbox 360 or PS3. I know it works on an Xbox One but I have not tested the voice into the Xbox but the audio works. Hope this helps"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work with ps4","answer":"Yes it does"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these work with the new Xbox One controller with 3.5mm jack without using the chat adapter?","answer":"Yes they do. Just plug the 3.5mm cable from the headset into the controller and your good to go."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is the audio quality 7.1 or 5.1?","answer":"I would say 5.1 virtual. They do sounds great if you have an optical connection."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you swap the ear cups?","answer":"There are plastic covers on the   outside   of the earpieces and one has an opening for the mic . . . and the other does not.  THOSE can be swapped.  So that the mic can go on either side.  But I see no way to swap the foam rubber ear covers."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this also for PC?","answer":"Yes."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does anyone know if the earcups are the same size as the A50? Or are they smaller or larger?","answer":"same size"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for ps4","answer":"Yes these are great set of headphones have lasted a long time and you work on a PS4 definitely would buy."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this be used with xbox 360?","answer":"Not out of the box, doesn't come with the small mic cable that plugs into the xbox controller. It might be viable with an adapter or the mix amp that astro offers."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If I buy these pc ones can I use them on my ps4?","answer":"Sadly not, unless you have usb microphone or a mix amp already it will not work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is this for the ps4 too?","answer":"I believe you need the astro mixamp if you want to use the mic. Otherwise they can work as a stereo headset. Waste though."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does ir come with the cables","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can these be used with the xbox 360?","answer":"I believe you need to get the amp/adapter to get it to work with Xbox 360. If go to the official website and chat with their representatives they can tell you exactly what parts to get."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"where is the volume control? How do I know if it is on the headphone or on the cord ?","answer":"It's on the cord"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Just received these. planning on using for my xbox1. do i have to have the mixamp for both game and chat audio?","answer":"Technically no. You could buy a Microsoft branded chat adapter and plug in the 3.5mm cable straight into the controller. However, I HIGHLY recommend you do not use this setup. The audio is in very bland stereo. Chat sounds fine but game audio is absolutely terrible compared to how the Mixamp will perform. You will need the Mixamp and a chat adapter (the chat adapter is necessary for the headset to be compatible with online chat so you will need the chat adapter either way) to get the most out of the headset which I definitely recommend. You could try using using just the chat adapter as you need it either way but I can guarantee the audio will be on a much lower grade scale as compared to the Mixamp."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this have mic monitoring? Thanks in advance.","answer":"Yes it does"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"he comes to mix amp","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"brand new for pc? and can warranty be claimed in singapore ?","answer":"This was a Christmas present for my nephew and I'm pretty sure it was for a game console although it should work for a pc with the appropriate jack."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can i use with the ps4 ???","answer":"Works perfectly with PS 4, by using the 3.5 jack with your Duel Shock Controller."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"These are not wireless correct?","answer":"Correct the wireless ones are the A50s"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can work for pc to","answer":"Yes it comes with a mic and headset splitter for your pc."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will these hurt my head from long play times?","answer":"I wear these for periods up to 8 hours without feeling pain, while wearing glasses.  They are very comfortable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it have or come with the two analog inputs and outputs (mic input and audio output cables)?","answer":"It comes with one mic input and one audio output from the main cable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with a stand","answer":"It does not but they used to have one listed on their site for around 20$ I believe. I do not see it listed anymore so you'd have to search eBay or Amazon for that as well."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with a mixamp","answer":"No unfortunately it does not :("}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it work for Xbox 360 and os4","answer":"Yes. If you get the correct mixamp for those controllers"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is it surround sound?","answer":"Only if you buy the Mixamp"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"If i buy the new mix amp pro will i get the 7.1 surround with these? Thanks.","answer":"Yes. But the source of audio needs to be able to output 7.1"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with the mix Amp","answer":"i ordered the orange pair and received the blue they came with an m80 mixamp for the Xbox one I ordered my own mixamp, so long story short, no it does not"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Using a 3rd party sound card (not the astro mix amp) can i still monitor my voice in the headset using the desktop app?","answer":"YES, you can. I use a app call realtek HD audio manager and turn on playback mircophone."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these Suround Sound capable and Will they reveal the direction of front-to-back sounds similar to a 5.1 speaker system?","answer":"Yes these are surround sound capable and they also do reveal the direction and I'm pretty sure it has similar speakers to 5.1 surround sound speakers in it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this include the mixamp?","answer":"no"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can work for pc to","answer":"yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with headphone stand","answer":"No is does not come with a stand. Just the headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with pc","answer":"Yes it does. The headset cable has audio and microphone input/output as one, so it can work on a Mac, phone, and even PS4 controller (I've tested it on all of these and it works beautifully). It comes with an adaptor to split the audio and microphone into two cables and it's a decent length. Pretty much plug-and-play."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this item for the Xbox one?","answer":"You would need either a xbox one chat adapter or astro mixamp"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does the headset work fine on ps4 without the mixamp and will you still be a able to talk?","answer":"Yes, I have a previous answer on another question that lays everything out in detail.  This question has been answered many many times.  It works great.  The headset does not have mic monitoring.  I really like it and I paid $150.  I'm jealous that it's $101 now.  The over the head band is made of a flexible neoprene material and the sides are aluminum, very strong and comfortable.  The boom mic can be switched to either side for whatever is more comfortable."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with the mixamp pro gen 1?","answer":"It should work with the mixamp. My friend uses the Mixamp with his normal PS4 A40's. However the A40's are fragile because after a couple of months of using the headset for the PS4 the headset microphone would not be able to pick up my voice. Not saying that you won't be careful its just that the A40's aren't as made well in my opinion as the A50's."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is this the 2015 version or the 2014?","answer":"My son said the posting was for Nov 1 2013 so he suspects it is a version 2014."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it cheaper to buy a mixamp bundled with this or seperate?","answer":"If you want better sound, get the mix amp. But it really isn't necessary. I got it without the mix amp and it still is great. I think the mix amp is kinda a waste."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I plug them into my Xbox headset adapter?","answer":"yes you can they will have the 3.5 mm headphone jack"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you use the PC headset with the ps4.","answer":"No, PS4 has a specific model for the series"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I am connecting these to my PC. Do I need a 7.1 Sound card? Or do I just need the mix amp?","answer":"You would be best off getting a good sound card especially if your mobo doesn't have TOSLink connection.  This is all you need to rock your gaming.    http://www.amazon.com/Blaster-Performance-Headphone-Forming-Microphone/dp/B009ISU33E/ref sr 1 3 m?s pc&ie UTF8&qid 1435176577&sr 1-3&keywords creative+labs"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use the mic if I plug it into a ps4 controller?","answer":"Yes, the headset has controls on the cable. You will only be able to adjust the total volume, and not adjust the game and speech individually with this headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Why has the price gone up over $50 in the last two days? The headset was $99 on 21 November...","answer":"This headset usually is this price. There was a sale going on before but it has now ended. ASTRO started this sale. Check their website now for more deals. It looks like they have 20% off right now on last gen headsets."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does with work with ps4 easily? Like i dont have to buy any other items and does it comes with mix amp?","answer":"This edition does not come with the mixamp. In my opinion, if you aren't an audiophile you will not miss it. As they provide excellent sound quality without. There are also no extra wires to bother with.   They do work with the PS4 without any extra equipment. Just plug into the 3.5mm jack in the controller and voice and audio work great."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is it 7.1or 5.1","answer":"7.1"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Mine didn't come with the mic or the cable please send me one thanks","answer":"you should really email the seller about that rather than post it as a question. or call customer service if purchased through amazon."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work on xbox 1","answer":"I am not sure about that but for the price I was not very happy with the ASTRO.  It need to be reset a lot and was very hot to wear."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How sensitive is the microphone? Will it pick up background noise such as people talking in other rooms or tv's?","answer":"No. It will not. If someone is right behind you even it normally doesnt even pick them up talking unless they are louder than normal. However, the mic itself if you are bumping it all the time it will pick this up. If you talk close into the mic itll come through loudly as well if you have it positioned normally it will be perfect while canceling out normal background noise."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this work well with Skype/Lync calls? I have an A30 and find it uncomfortable due to that model being on-ear, so looking to upgrade.","answer":"in my experience the headset didnt work at all. if your going to spend some money just get tritons or whatever else you prefer"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use it to listen to music and make phone calls on my smart phone?","answer":"Yeah sure. Also good for this"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this use separate game and chat volume controls?","answer":"Only if you have a mix amp or software such as Razer surround or audible that will do it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it work on the ps4? Can you talk in a party with this mic?","answer":"Quoted from Astro rep  It is compatible for audio only. You would need our mixamp in order to use the microphone on your PS4 though. " So you would need a mixamp to use the mic on your PS4 but you can use the headphones as headphones only.""}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have astro mixamp 5.8 system and xbox one stereo adapter. will these headphones work on my setup?  do i get better sound if i don't use the adapter?","answer":"Because this is a more technical question I would recommend contacting ASTRO gaming support. However I believe it is the same headset with just a different look to it. I don't believe it will give you better sound but i do believe it will work."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Windows 10 compatible?","answer":"Yes, there is no driver required. It just plugs into the pink and green audio jacks in your computer."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you need mix amp for audio and microphone for ps4?","answer":"No, the PC version plugs directly into the PS4.  The volume on the inline mic will adjust both audio and mic volume simultaneously.  Remember as you turn down audio you are also turning down mic volume for other people hearing you.  Adjust the mix in game or in Party chats."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How good is the build? Does it last longer than 1 year?","answer":"It's very durable. I have worn it almost every day for just under a year, have knocked it off my desk many times, had my cat yank the cord so the mid-line connection gets unplugged roughly, had my cat bite at the microphone some, and the headset still works perfectly.  The ear padding is still soft, clean, and is not frayed, despite me sometimes wearing the headset over scratchy earrings."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I just connect this to my ps4 dual shock 4 controller for audio and chat? Without the mixamp","answer":"Yes you can"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Dosse it work with ps4","answer":"yea but to get the full experience go to audio settings a select headset audio to all, making all the game and chat audio go through the headset."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have an Xbox one, and a turtle beach adapter, will it work perfectly if I just plug in some astros?plz help!","answer":"Yes. But you're stuck with being able to hear yourself when not in a party. So I suggest buying the first party adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can I use this a40 the one that's worth 120 dollars on ps4 I have to be sure and people are giving mixed answers","answer":"Yes, I use my A40 on my PC and PS4 so it shouldn't be a problem."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do i need the mix amp for just using it with the PC?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with the original box ?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I know this sounds like a silly question but the word  kit " makes me uneasy. I want the headset but is it a headset or is it just like some parts?"","answer":"By kit,they mean you are getting a few enhancements,like a mobile cable,a PC Splitter/Adapter,etc"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"this headset have the mixamp?","answer":"mixamp comes seperately"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it cause echoing on the xbox one still?","answer":"I am Not sure I use them on a PC."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have a ASUS XONAR DG, would this be a good substitute for the mix amp? or should I move up to a 7.1 version?","answer":"Go with 7.1"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you have use a specific mixamp because I have the mixamp pro","answer":"It works with all astro mixamps"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"You may have got this question, but I do not want to throwaway $300 for nothing, but is this headset from 2015?","answer":"Yup, but they're for half that price here so I recommend getting this offer..."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it work with Xbox One?","answer":"With the chat adapter for xbox one remotes, bith the headphones and microphone will work plugged in to the controller. It's one of the main reasons i bought it, cross compatability.    Or you could wait until the new controller comes out that has the port already built in."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"will it work with ps4?","answer":"I think you will need the mix amp for the PS4, sadly my ps4 is under the tree atm waiting for christmas so if you can wait till the 25th I can really answer this LOL"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"By default, can you hear your own voice without lag when talking using this headset?  My current headset makes it hard to hear myself so I shout :(","answer":"This headset does not natively have this feature, however the software application you use might. For example mumble has a voice playback feature which may help."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i buy this with euros??","answer":"No I am sorry"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How is the bass (I like heavy bass)?  And do I need an amp for these since they are 48ohms?","answer":"The bass is not bad to get the bass you want you need to check the frequency specs,below 15 HZ  I know the bass you want, but you have to spend a lot more money, no you do not need an amp,they are comfy"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with the mic","answer":"yes. It comes with mic in box."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will they work on my ps4 and do they come with a mixamp?","answer":"Yes they work on ps4 and comes with a mix amp. I'm very happy with the quality of them"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are the ear cups foldable?","answer":"No sorry"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these mountain dew proof?","answer":"Depends what type of mountain dew."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Are these the 2nd Gen A40's?","answer":"Yes this is new version"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it comes with everything","answer":"Yup. Erryting you need mon.   It is the best headphones I've ever had."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is it comfortable","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does it come or can it be used with a usb wire","answer":"no"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this come with a mix amp???","answer":"No, you have to buy it separate unless they have a special bundle available."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can you use these this with ps3","answer":"No, the only reason it works with the PS4 is the standard headphone jack plugs directly into the controller.  The PS3 needs a headset with a USB connection."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"DOes it work with Xbox 360 or do you need the mixamp or chat cord?","answer":"This was a gift for my son.  I asked him and he said that you need a chat cord."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Difference between these and http://www.amazon.com/astro-gaming-a40-system-bundle-xbox/dp/b00o9n404q/ref sr 1 1?s videogames&ie utf8&qid 1439432941&sr","answer":"get tritons man Only a few buck more and its such a better product"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"They work for ps4","answer":"Yes, they work great with 3.5 jack on the PS 4 duel shock controller. I use it that way all the time."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How is the pressure? I am very sensitive to even slightly too much squeezing.","answer":"There is very little pressure while using the headset. I'm also very sensitive with the headset pressure."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can i use this on the xbox one with out the amp","answer":"I ordered mine without the amp because I didn't feel like paying extra for something like that. Without the amp, the headset cord is split, one for headphone jack, and one for mic.  I'm still trying to think of the best way to go about using them for consoles."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"can u hear footsteps","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have a mixamp pro can use these with it? And still getting surround sound? And voice chat on xbox one with my adaptor?","answer":"Yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do you need the mix amp for the headset to work","answer":"No. If using on a PC it is basically plug and play. But if you want to say use it on a Xbox 1, you will need the adapter which is also readily available at Amazon.com. FYI my son 'loves' these headphones, and says that the sound quality is better than his more expensive set of Beats headphones."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can i use this on all my consoles?(xbox 360, ps3/4)","answer":"You can't with this alone. You'd need to get the Astro Mixamp to be able to use it on consoles."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can this work with an xbox one with the adpater???","answer":"Yes but the audio is not very good. I recommend using the Mixamp and the adapter. The adapter I use for just voice chat"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What do these come with do they come with a charging stand like the Astro a50s","answer":"no they dont they are plug and play"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"does this work with pc","answer":"Yes, of course it does. I have had my own for many years now."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this mean that it comes ready to be use with my PC, or do i have to buy Separate cables?","answer":"It's ready to use for the PC, Mac and mobile phones."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do they work with Xbox One system?","answer":"If you have the Xbox controller stereo headset adapter then yes"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will it work on ps3","answer":"i used the astro a40 WITH the astro mixamp on ps3 for a long time. the mic works perfectly online and the sound is the best you can get. all you have to do is plug an optical cable from the mixamp to the back of the ps3 and a usb from the mixamp to the ps3 and you have sound and a mic"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how do you receive calls using this? how does it work?","answer":"I had to buy a small adapter so that would plug into the side of our phone. We have had other headphones but this one is so much better.  My husband makes a lot of business calls while he is typing on his computer and this helps with that.  Our phone just has one button he pushes to answer when he has his headset on."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this model work with a Plantronic CT14?","answer":"Hi April, this headset will not work with a Plantronics CT14. You will need to get a cordless or corded home phone to connect this headset with. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"do i need any special cord or adapter to use with Yealink T42G phones?","answer":"Hi Teresa.  To use this with that model Yealink phone, you'll want to get this cord.  http://www.amazon.com/dp/B0007INITA.  Please feel free to give us a call if you have any other questions.  1-800-432-3738"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I work from home and have the kids around for some meetings-will it block out most of their joyful noise?","answer":"You hear whatever you are listening to very well, but I think you may still hear the kids."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have an old panasonic kx-tsc55 2-line phone. will this plug in directly to that phone's out jack? does it have a mute switch?","answer":"Here is what I bought to attach it to my Panasonic landline phone.  Sennheiser CCEL190-2 Headset Cable-Adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I need an rj9 plug with this headset? How to accomplish this?","answer":"Hi Janine!  You'll want the Sennheiser CSTD-01 cord. It's a quick-disconnect to RJ9 connector cord. Link below.  https://www.amazon.com/Sennheiser-005362-CSTD01-Cable-Adapter/dp/B0007INITA/ref pd bxgy 229 img 2? encoding UTF8&pd rd i B0007INITA&pd rd r QSJMKPE0RCX6WA51AM0M&pd rd w n7qLH&pd rd wg Lq0lz&psc 1&refRID QSJMKPE0RCX6WA51AM0M  -Headsets.com"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Would this work for a cellphone (Samsung Galaxy S5)?","answer":"Hi, Mel.  This version of the DeskMate can be adapted to fit any phone.  However, in most states (maybe all) it is illegal to drive with a dual ear headset on for your cell phone.  If you're only going to use this to listen to music etc, I'd check out this adapter.  https://www.amazon.com/Sennheiser-Quick-Disconnect-adapter-Smartphone/dp/B00OHVUOHM/ref sr 1 1?s electronics&ie UTF8&qid 1477067236&sr 1-1&keywords 506090"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this phone work with a siemens optipoint 410 advance phone? what attachment would i need to connect it via the headset jack?","answer":"Yes this headset works. You'll need the adapter with part number CLS 01. Feel free to call in at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is the microphone noise cancelling?","answer":"Yes! The microphone is noise-canceling.  -Headsets.com"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will this work with a standard cordless house phone?","answer":"Hi Ben. We have a DeskMate bundle that comes with the 2.5mm connection that you will want to connect to your cordless home phone.  Here is the link to that bundle https://www.amazon.com/Sennheiser-DeskMate-Dual-Ear-Cordless-Phone/dp/B00JS81SSI?ie UTF8& Version  1& entries  0  and please give us a call if you have any other questions on this.  1-800-432-3738"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"how do I connect this to an iPhone 7+? Do I need an adapter?","answer":"Hi Cathy!  You'll want the Quick Disconnect to 3.5mm cord. :-)  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00OHVUOHM"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Hi all, i want to connect these to my phone jack on my office phone. what connector(s) come with the headset? thank you!","answer":"One that fits a standard telephone (landline type). Cell phones require another connector which has to be purchased separately."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does this Headset have a replaceable microphone?","answer":"No"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Can you hear your own voice in the headset?","answer":"No. This is the best headset on the market besides possibly the ridiculously expensive 3-400 dollar audiophiles options, if you have an amp or soundcard to drive them. Only thing that is better is a dedicated pair of equally expensive headphones and a blue snowball mic."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Will the microphone work with a mixamp setup on the PS4?","answer":"I believe it should as you get 2 cables you can switch between - one with single 3.5 mic+headphones and one with split mic and headphone. It works with PS out of the box. The microphone quality is incredible though."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Wanting to use this headset for both xbox one x and my ps4 pro. to get the full effect will i need to pair a mix amp with it?","answer":"That I do not know. I use mine for PC"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I have a hyperx, but am dissapointed in the microphone.  the mic on the hyperx is not as loud as i need it.  anyone know how this one compares?","answer":"I use this headset daily on discord and video games such as PUBG, Rainbow six, and Rust. My discord buddies often have to tell me to turn myself down or move the microphone piece far away from my mouth, because this microphone  amplifies pretty well. I also tend to just speak very loudly. As far as I'm concerned, this microphone works almost too well!     It will also help to be aware of your PC settings. there are hidden sliders all over the place that could be affecting how loud you're sounding to those on the other side."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I bought these used and when raise the mic too high it unmutes and people hear you really low, does this happen to everyone else?","answer":"Once you hear/feel the click from turning the mic up, it should mute you. Any further up could damage it? I'm not sure, but sometimes I move my mic a bit up above my nose to drink while gaming, and others can barely hear me. Hope this helps."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"What's the difference between the single 3.5mm cable and the split 3.5mm mic/headphones cable?","answer":"The single cable is likely for use on things like cellphones. I hadn't tried it as I intended to use it on my PC but it definitely makes sense, as there are already headsets and earbuds with mics on them for that purpose."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these have an aux input so that a cell phone can in patched in?","answer":"No, these dont have aux inout."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Is there any additional items I need to purchase in order to use with my Xbox one ?!","answer":"you need to buy the pcv 05 aduio adapter"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"I'm playing in a room with a lot of noise. does the nose canceling really works?","answer":"The noise isolation on the microphone is pretty good, but this headset is open backed meaning it allows background noise through. If you are in a noisy environment the Game Zero is a better option because it is closed back."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does anyone else have issues with the audio cutting out every so often or did I receive a lemon? Is the Zero sound quality better?","answer":"I have never had any sort of glitch with this headset. The sound has been great from day one."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Does it come with the cable for console","answer":"Yes! The Game One comes with both a PC cable and a console cable.    Kind Regards,  Sennheiser Gaming"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How do these feel while wearing glasses for an extended period of time?","answer":"I don't wear glasses personally, but the person who recommended this headset to me wears glasses, and wears them for at least 5 hours a day, so I would hazard a guess that it is relatively comfortable, as he is not someone who would put up with an uncomfortable headset for him."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"How good is the microphone quality?","answer":"Its actully really good.  when i play with ny friends and i need to be quiet, they never said that they can't hear me."}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"is their an attachment that I can use to connect this to a desk phone?","answer":"it didn't come with one but someone may make an adaptor for it"}
{"index":{"_index":"nlp_pqa"}}
{"question":"Do these have more bass than the game zeros?","answer":"Due to the closed back design the Game ZERO will have more perceived bass."}
